@ich_ayu/O :/O Yaelah/O maryam/PERSON ./O nyewa/O mobil/O masak/O ke/O kbri/ORGANIZATION
<90>/O BPTJ/O Targetkan/O 60/O Persen/O Warga/O Jadebotabek/LOCATION Naik/O Angkutan/O Umum/O ./O https://t/O .co/SyLbxZv3Jw/O ./O
@hellodinaSF/O :/O HMJ/ORGANIZATION Akuntansi/O
@victormadjid/O :/O @SiahaanSabeth/O nah/O itu/O MNC/ORGANIZATION nggak/O suka/O artis/O SCTV/ORGANIZATION begitupun/O sebaliknya/O apalagi/O ada/O koalisi/O media/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Selamat/O berjuang/O para/O pengurus/O DPC/O Kabupaten/O Kuningan/LOCATION ,/O Indramayu/LOCATION ,/O Cirebon/LOCATION dan/O Kota/O Cirebon/LOCATION ./O Cirebon/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/0LeCEw6MSd/O
@prabowo/O :/O @ilyas_69762/O Terima/O kasih/O ./O
@infoBMKG/O :/O Titik/O ketujuh/O di/O jalur/O totalitas/O #GMT9Mar16/O adalah/O Ternate/LOCATION ,/O Maluku/LOCATION Utara/LOCATION ./O Tepatnya/O di/O Pantai/LOCATION Palajawa/LOCATION samping/O Masjid/LOCATION Almunawar/LOCATION ,/O Ternate/LOCATION ./O
@detikcom/O :/O Kontroversi/O Beda/O Hadiah/O Uang/O Tenis/O Putra-Putri/O https://t.co/De8HBLgvWL/O via/O @detiksport/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O pembully/O juga/O harus/O pinter/O geografi/O mas/O ./O https://t.co/81xUfidrlF/O
@Gramedia_SS/O :/O Grameds/O yg/O mau/O ikut/O lomba/O mewarnai/O dewasa/O besok/O ada/O lomba/O di/O Gramedia/LOCATION JCM/LOCATION @gramediajcm/O Jogja/LOCATION ./O Syaratnya/O gampang/O bgt/O https://t.co/90FxGyy7Re/O
@aagym/O :/O 1/O milyar/O ,/O bukan/O masalah/O jumlah/O nol/O ,/O tapi/O berkahkah/O cara/O mendapatkannya/O ,/O dipergunakan/O Utk/O apa/O ,/O semuanya/O akan/O dihisab/O https://t.co/8xHmOHgxn3/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O @PuspitaFM/O Perda/O 1/O thn/O 2012/O ttg/O Bangunan/O Gedung/O telah/O mewajibkan/O setiap/O rumah/O ada/O sumur/O resapannya/O @MalangGreenCity/O @BappedaMalang/O
@Kabupaten_Bogor/O :/O Wisata/O Alam/O yang/O ada/O di/O Kab./O Bogor/LOCATION nih/O :/O https://t.co/d930Bz3lBO/O
@aagym/O :/O Seringkali/O kita/O sibuk/O dengan/O kecemasan/O akibat/O mendramatisir/O masalah/O ,/O padahal/O sesudah/O dilalui/O tak/O Segawat/O yang/O dicemaskan/O
@aizzatsyazwan/O :/O Lagi/O muda/O beli/O lagi/O bagus/O
@FadhlinaLatif/O :/O "/O jatuh/O cinta/O sama/O artis/O "/O
@Zaza_Zizu/O :/O RT/O @zulazry/O :/O Kepanasan/O melampau/O ./O Suhu/O hari/O ini/O 40/O celcius/O sehingga/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Kontestasi/O politik/O merupakan/O pengalaman/O yang/O baru/O bagi/O saya/O ./O Saya/O gembira/O bisa/O ikut/O konvensi/O dan/O mendapat/O banyak/O pelajaran/O ./O
@aagym/O :/O Bagi/O yang/O sangat/O senang/O dipuji/O dan/O dikagumi/O manusia/O niscaya/O akan/O sangat/O sibuk/O membangun/O topeng/O dan/O bungkus/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @CucuJendrall/O :/O @infomalang/O bagi/O yang/O menemukan/O dompet/O hitam/O panjang/O di/O daerah/O pasar/LOCATION samaan/LOCATION mohon/O hubungi/O nmr/O 085648861233/O ./O
@sultonbpn/O :/O RT/O @dimasprakbar/O :/O yang/O merk/O apa/O ya/O ?/O RT/O @Bisniscom/O :/O 180/O Bus/O Transjakarta/O Dihancurkan/O https://t.co/DVNNdjBuz9/O https://t.co/4diJhDAv8u/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selamat/O siang/O ,/O kemarin/O saya/O berkesempatan/O mengikuti/O upacara/O pelepasan/O 52/O tank/O Leopard/O dari/O 164/O unit/O yang/O dipesan/O pemerintah/O RI/ORGANIZATION di/O Jerman/LOCATION ./O
@nifamaula/O :/O RT/O @JakmaniaPnrg/O :/O Persija/ORGANIZATION Jakarta/LOCATION akan/O melakukan/O ujicoba/O melawan/O Africa/LOCATION Selection/O ,/O 2/4/2016/O Pkl/O ./O 07:30/O wib/O di/O Std.Cendrawasih/LOCATION -/O Cengkareng/LOCATION ./O
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O sibuk/O berkomentar/O yang/O tak/O dipahami/O dan/O tak/O perlu/O dikomentari/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O Pataka/O kepada/O perwakilan/O DPC-DPC/O Kab/O ./O Sumedang/LOCATION ,/O Kab/O ./O Bandung/LOCATION dan/O Kota/O Bandung/LOCATION ./O Rabu/O 2/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/vCppqR5qc3/O
@ilmujatuhcinta/O :/O STAFF/O AUDITOR/O PT./ORGANIZATION WATERINDEX/ORGANIZATION TIRTA/ORGANIZATION LESTARI/ORGANIZATION ,/O LAMPUNG/LOCATION
<73>/O Penyesalan/O Terbesar/O Inzaghi/PERSON terkait/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/X0QTWDsk8B/O
@infodishub/O :/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION DORONG/O PEMBANGUNAN/O MONOREL/O http://t.co/Dm6ycTUsDp/O #BeritaPusat/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O lawan/O dengan/O inovasi/O ./O bersama-sama/O ./O Dgn/O semangat/O kayak/O film/O Titanic/O "/O Antum/O jump/O ,/O Ana/O Jump/O "/O https://t.co/UHPJPqmUnC/O
@rajajobs/O :/O Lowongan/O di/O PT/ORGANIZATION Ezy/ORGANIZATION Informatika/ORGANIZATION
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Mantan/O Mentan/O Jamin/O Penangguhan/O Penahanan/O Guru/O Honorer/O https://t.co/03sOEdLwDL/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Saya/O tadi/O hadir/O sebagai/O undangan/O di/O Rapat/O Fraksi/O Partai/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION DPR-RI/ORGANIZATION ./O Ada/O beberapa/O poin/O yang/O ingin/O saya/O sampaikan/O di/O sini/O ./O
@detiksport/O :/O Bos/O Bayern/ORGANIZATION :/O Jauhi/O Pemain/O Kami/O ,/O City/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/Mt4Vwb2vrb/O
<52>/O Ini/O Aksi/O “/O Drift/O Gila/O ”/O Ken/O Block/O Episode/O ke-9/O ./O https://t/O .co/Ms5O2QXNbQ/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menyerahkan/O cenderamata/O kepada/O Marsekal/O TNI/ORGANIZATION Purnawirawan/O Herman/PERSON Prayitno/PERSON ,/O Duta/O Besar/O Indonesia/LOCATION untuk/O Malaysia/LOCATION ./O https://t.co/Sk9ieH02Od/O
@mashendra_mas/O :/O Sebelum/O Serahkan/O Data/O Transaksi/O ,/O BNI/ORGANIZATION Syariah/O Koordinasi/O dengan/O Asosiasi/O
@prabowo/O :/O @brajahariandja1/O Mohon/O sampaikan/O salam/O duka/O saya/O kepada/O seluruh/O keluarga/O ./O Terima/O kasih/O ./O
@basuki_btp/O :/O RT/O @imadya:/O Stand/O up/O comedy/O @Metro_TV/O ada/O Ahok/PERSON !/O
<11>/O Kafe/LOCATION Bertema/O "Friends"/O Segera/O Dibuka/O di/O Singapura/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/qgnOJYRqT6/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Memberi/O Pengarahan/O kepada/O Pejabat/O Struktural/O Kementerian/O Tenaga/O Kerja/O https://t.co/yodnKNyGqU/O
@inilahdotcom/O :/O Cara/O Smartfren/ORGANIZATION Edukasi/O Masyarakat/O Layanan/O 4G/O LTE/O https://t.co/N7RjENOtd7/O https://t.co/fNvpURZuJt/O
@infodishub/O :/O Menhub/O :/O Perlu/O Pemilihan/O Teknologi/O ERP/O yang/O Baik/O http://t.co/FWhoEzHPcy/O #BeritaPusat/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O kepada/O semua/O yang/O merayakan/O ,/O Selamat/O tahun/O baru/O Imlek/O ./O Gong/O Xi/O Fa/O Cai/O !/O https://t.co/8dZAMvuQyF/O
@beritabaruu/O :/O Jangan/O takut/O mencoba/O hal/O yang/O baru/O ,/O gapailah/O impianmu/O ./O
@Ester_Unyu/O :/O Karawang/LOCATION pastikan/O tarif/O angkutan/O umum/O turun/O
@aagym/O :/O Sekecil/O apapun/O kebaikan/O orang/O ,/O kita/O harus/O berterima/O kasih/O dan/O sebesar/O apapun/O kebaikan/O kita/O ,/O tak/O perlu/O menunggu/O ucapan/O terimakasih/O
@prabowo/O :/O Jangan/O kita/O jadi/O partai/O besar/O tapi/O berisi/O maling-maling/O ./O Lebih/O baik/O kecil/O tapi/O bersih/O dari/O maling-maling/O ./O Bersih/O dari/O para/O komprador/O ./O
@cinta_energi/O :/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION Akan/O Coba/O Gandeng/O Kementerian/O Pariwisata/O Untuk/O Membantu/O Rio/PERSON Haryanto/PERSON
@ridwankamil/O :/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION ./O #YNWA/O https://t.co/BKwsaplI7T/O
@infoMinangkabau/O :/O #Radar/O Kota/O Padang/O melalui/O citra/O satelit/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Indonesia/LOCATION Rayu/O Tiga/O Negara/O ini/O untuk/O Dapat/O Stok/O Minyak/O https://t.co/BA0bxgBQzL/O
@keyla12350/O :/O @jedarcantik/O yo/O idolaku/O yg/O tegas/O spt/O bu/O ayu/PERSON biar/O g/O kyk/O skg/O
@fattah407/O :/O @UCBrowserIndo/O SEMUT/O ,/O yg/O menyimbolkan/O penuh/O kekompakan/O ,/O kerja/O keras/O dan/O gotong/O royong/O #UCBrowserAprilMop/O
@PengejarBerita/O :/O REI/O Minta/O Pemda/ORGANIZATION Bisa/O Turunkan/O BPHTB/O
@RizkiSaputaa/O :/O Mencinta/O adalah/O membahagiakan/O satu/O sama/O lain/O ,/O bukan/O menuntut/O satu/O pihak/O untuk/O membahagiakan/O pihak/O lain/O ./O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Selamat/O bertanding/O untuk/O Mitra/ORGANIZATION Kukar/ORGANIZATION dan/O Semen/ORGANIZATION Padang/ORGANIZATION ./O Utamakan/O fair/O play/O ./O ./O #PialaJenderalSudirman/O
@MicheleZuya/O :/O Cigna/ORGANIZATION Hadirkan/O Family/O Proteksi/O Optima/O
@SiitiHajar_/O :/O (/O deadline/O mak/O ooiiiiiiii/O )/O HIDUPLAH/O INDONESIA/LOCATION RAYA/O
@infodishub/O :/O PENUMPANG/O KERETA/O API/O MENINGKAT/O http://t.co/9CqXKQUrd7/O #BeritaPusat/O
<31>/O Mengenal/O ADHD/O ,/O Penyebab/O Hiperaktif/O pada/O Anak/O https://t/O .co/XxLFeECUJ3/O https://t/O .co/DumOLxpdLC/O
@solikhatii/O :/O Istiqosah/O (/O Lapangan/LOCATION SMKN/O 1/O Surabaya/LOCATION )/O https://t.co/PxykDRumRl/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O program/O konversi/O 3/O angkot/O menjadi/O 1/O bus/O kota/O ./O https://t.co/zrBBksAjWD/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selalu/O ingat/O ,/O '/O di/O mana/O bumi/O berpijak/O ,/O di/O sana/O langit/O dijunjung/O ./O '/O Sukses/O bagi/O peserta/O #IndonesiaMengajar/O yg/O akan/O berangkat/O minggu/O ini/O ./O
@nurulnrh/O :/O Anak/O 2/O ini/O aku/O dijadikan/O kambing/O congek/O (/O Shiva/PERSON Alun-Alun/LOCATION Kota/O Malang/LOCATION )/O https://t.co/zdcD4Eoq3Z/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Ini/O Skema/O Aneh/O Real/ORGANIZATION Madrid/ORGANIZATION untuk/O Seorang/O Alvaro/PERSON Morata/PERSON https://t.co/RvyYKhvkdd/O
@ZahirAccounting/O :/O cara/O kurangi/O jenuh/O hadapi/O pekerjaan/O Akuntansi/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Sementara/O ,/O Partai/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION konsisten/O utk/O katakan/O "/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION Tetap/O NON-BLOK/O ,/O Tak/O Masuk/O KIH/ORGANIZATION &/O Tak/O Masuk/O KMP/ORGANIZATION "/O ./O Ya/O ,/O Non-Blok/O ./O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @Pacitanku/O :/O Kala/O 1001/O Siswa/O di/O Pacitan/LOCATION Tiup/O Seruling/O di/O Hari/O Jadi/O Pacitan/LOCATION ke/O 271/O https://t.co/AKuwSXwmfA/O https://t.co/Y8VE2aZ5eG/O
<40>/O Hari/O Kunjung/O Perpustakaan/O ,/O Upaya/O Dongkrak/O Minat/O Baca/O Masyarakat/O https://t/O .co/RZq3Q3QeCs/O https://t/O .co/LJzuPJvHxG/O
@radityadika/O :/O Uh/O ./O ./O https://t.co/7yTqNqLSYU/O
<18>/O Jalan-Jalan/O Super/O Seru/O Bareng/O Si/O Cantik/O Jessica/PERSON Mila/PERSON https://t.co/00l1NHI4kx/O https://t.co/U986ks80Qi/O
@prabowo/O :/O RT/O @aburizalbakrie/O :/O 5/O ./O Demikian/O penjelasan/O dari/O saya/O tentang/O hasil/O keputusan/O Mahkamah/O Partai/O ./O Semoga/O bermanfaat/O ./O yang/O ingin/O mengutip/O
@woofnod/O :/O @zbdshdan_/O aku/O jumpa/O dia/O gotong/O royong/O di/O masjid/O
@ArunaNilna/O :/O RT/O @ofcprllvrs:/O Hai/O Prillvers/O MANADO/LOCATION join/O gath/O nya/O yaaaa/O dan/O perayaan/O annive/O PV/O 57/O bulan/O di/O kota/O kalian/O !/O @Prillvers__MDO/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Selamat/O Tahun/O Baru/O #Imlek/O 2567/O bagi/O yang/O merayakan/O ./O Semoga/O selalu/O damai/O ,/O makmur/O dan/O bahagia/O ./O
@detikcom/O :/O Saat/O Gerhana/O ,/O Ayam-ayam/O di/O Ternate/LOCATION Lebih/O Tenang/O dan/O Masuk/O ke/O Kandang/LOCATION https://t.co/B6ColujoSv/O
@infomalang/O :/O #cuacamalang/O RT/O @hildarahma17/O :/O Jl/LOCATION ./O jombang/LOCATION Petir/O ambk/O bledeg/O sak/O udan/O e/O ngotot/O ya/O Allah/O hati-hati/O yang/O diluar/O rumah/LOCATION
@mitraloker/O :/O Guru/O Akuntansi/O ,/O Matematika/O ,/O Biologi/O ,/O Fisika/O
@jokowi/O :/O Setujukah/O orang/O yang/O buang/O sampah/O sembarangan/O tidak/O memiliki/O tanggung/O jawab/O sosial/O ?/O -/O Jkw/PERSON
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @dwi_aprianto/O :/O mohon/O infonya/O untuk/O pawai/O ogoh2/O jelang/O hari/O raya/O nyepi/O di/O Malang/LOCATION ada/O gak/O ./O ya/O ?/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Mendengarkan/O harapan/O &/O aspirasi/O rakyat/O ,/O Jika/O pemerintah/O baik/O kita/O dukung/O ,/O namun/O jika/O kurang/O tepat/O kita/O kritisi/O #SBYTourDeJava/O
@hananghanuri/O :/O Juwita/PERSON nangis/O minta/O izin/O nonton/O artis/O favoritnya/O tp/O dilarang/O ibunya/O lalu/O disuruh/O cuci/O piring/O Haha/O kasihan/O @Ini_Talkshow/O #StereoDiIniTalkshow/O
@radityadika/O :/O Mitos/O ./O https://t.co/sMO9cH7akT/O
@AmosSulistiawan/O :/O Lomba/O Desain/O Bumper/O Sticker/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION !/O
@Ehhh_najwa/O :/O RT/O @aqilahnasrin/O :/O hargailah/O detik/O anda/O di/O sekolah/LOCATION hahahah/O https://t.co/SOD5D6p2tV/O
@Kabupaten_Bogor/O :/O SSA/O Hari/O Pertama/O Dievaluasi/O ,/O Berikut/O Perubahan/O yang/O Akan/O Dieksekusi/O https://t.co/u57UJQfHKz/O #heibogor/O
@BKNSquare/O :/O STAFF/O AUDITOR/O PT./ORGANIZATION WATERINDEX/ORGANIZATION TIRTA/ORGANIZATION LESTARI/ORGANIZATION ,/O LAMPUNG/LOCATION
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O Wakil/O Rektor/O ,/O Dekan/O ,/O Ketua/O Senat/O dan/O Guru/O Besar/O Universitas/ORGANIZATION Trisakti/ORGANIZATION ./O Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O Sabtu/O 27/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/HfU0zxnKKa/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Kemlu/O Pastikan/O Ada/O WNI/O Jadi/O Korban/O Bom/O Belgia/LOCATION https://t.co/VfjnRmNUVI/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O kalo/O ama/O preman/O maksa2/O warga/O kyk/O gitu/O ,/O saya/O pasti/O kasar/O ./O support/O kota/O tertib/O ./O https://t.co/fdcFDDjcIr/O
@melvin_ghiffari/O :/O PENDIDIKAN/O CIAMIS/LOCATION ,/O -/O Ujian/O nasional/O berbasis/O komputer/O https://t.co/IyV83cpgTf/O
@FilantropiCloth/O :/O Cinta/O itu/O tulus/O ./O Bahkan/O ketika/O kemarahan/O mulai/O muncul/O ,/O tidak/O akan/O pernah/O menuntut/O untuk/O dimengerti/O ./O Konveksi/O Distro/O
@SeptyPtr/O :/O Pertama/O nya/O ngeliat/O buku/O akuntansi/O
@infomalang/O :/O @nda_anin/O cek/O di/O FB/ORGANIZATION coba/O ,/O ada/O grup/O https://t.co/lmUJCRDTTe/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Insya/O Allah/O bulan/O depan/O akan/O kita/O mulai/O ./O siap2/O aja/O ./O https://t.co/xRz8znUKTH/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Wahai/O keluarga/O yang/O mapan/O ,/O mari/O bergabung/O menjadi/O keluarga/O asuh/O ./O Silih/O asah/O asih/O ,/O asuh/O ./O Hatur/O Nuhun/O ./O https://t.co/fKPp4uyG0z/O
@threefmaceh/O :/O Bupati/O Bireuen/LOCATION Gotong/O Royong/O Bersama/O Bersihkan/O Waduk/O https://t.co/snb1eW6hBo/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O NOAH/O Buka/O HUT/O ANTV/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/Lz5LKC4qSv/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O BPJS/O (/O kesehatan/O )/O sangat/O dibutuhkan/O ./O Terus/O ditingkatkan/O dulu/O fasilitas/O (/O sarpras/O )/O ,/O pelayanan/O &/O asuransi/O yg/O didapatkan/O https://t.co/a1w0NB6Bd3/O
@ulfarizkiaa/O :/O RT/O @SCTV_/O :/O Yuk/O nonton/O penampilan/O @fstvlst/O pkl/O 19.00/O WIB/O di/O #ToraCinoCoolExpression/O Yuk/O langsung/O datang/O ke/O kampus/O UMY/ORGANIZATION ,/O Jogja/LOCATION
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @SemangatPositif/O :/O Saat/O kita/O mengkritik/O orang/O lain/O ,/O pastikan/O kritikan/O kita/O membangkitan/O prestasi/O ,/O bukan/O malah/O menjadikannya/O frustasi/O ./O
<40>/O 6/O Adegan/O Kocak/O Warkop/O DKI/LOCATION Reborn/O yang/O Bikin/O Ngakak/O https://t.co/QSdkoNroOM/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Tujuh/O Orang/O Paling/O Misterius/O di/O Dunia/O https://t.co/mbT0If445p/O
@amieyraa_/O :/O makanan/O depan/O rumah/O
<65>/O Aksi/O Jual/O Masih/O Berlangsung/O di/O Lantai/O Bursa/O ,/O IHSG/O Dibuka/O Melemah/O ./O https://t/O .co/oZyWQDtMje/O
<36>/O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON dan/O Ironi/O Masyarakat/O Urban/O ./O https://t/O .co/g2CDLCobjA/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O 3/O ./O Pemerintah/O hanya/O mampu/O menyiapkan/O 4/O jt/O lapangan/O pekerjaan/O ./O Sedangkan/O dunia/O usaha/O mampu/O menyiapkan/O 100/O jt/O tenaga/O kerja/O ./O #munaskadin/O
@infomalang/O :/O @mahastrahamdan/O di/O dalam/O pasar/LOCATION besar/O/LOCATION ada/O ,/O di/O centerpoint/O mog/LOCATION jg/O biasanya/O ada/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O Teman-teman/O ,/O terimakasih/O utk/O dukungannya/O yg/O luar/O biasa/O ini/O ./O Saya/O masih/O Plt/O gubernur/O ,/O menunggu/O pelantikan/O nanti/O ./O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Arahan/O Ketum/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION dalam/O Pelantikan/O Pengurus/O DPC/O se/O -/O Kalimantan/LOCATION Selatan/LOCATION ./O Banjarmasin/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 3/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/PWOUOO6QpJ/O
@detiksport/O :/O Kane/PERSON Menjaga/O Spurs/PERSON Tetap/O di/O Jalur/O Juara/O https://t.co/im2R5tlvr5/O https://t.co/vgfqm9pvYq/O
@aainaa_namr/O :/O RT/O @FoodPornMlaysia/O :/O Nama/O artis/O boleh/O retweet/O takkan/O nama/O yang/O indah/O ini/O tak/O boleh/O ?/O http://t.co/ZBbihBpoaV/O
@aagym/O :/O Kepada/O ahli/O jogging/O atau/O yang/O suka/O jalan/O jalan/O ke/O dalam/O dan/O luar/O negri/O ,/O silakan/O tafakuri/O poster/O ini/O ya/O https://t.co/DFMp67VNuO/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O Ke/O depan/O saya/O mengharapkan/O pemerintahan/O Jokowi/PERSON -/O JK/PERSON tetap/O melibatkan/O putra/O putri/O terbaik/O bangsa/O seperti/O Eva/PERSON ,/O Rieke/PERSON &/O Ara/PERSON ./O
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O bangga/O rakyat/O Indonesia/LOCATION tidak/O takut/O hadapi/O teroris/O ./O Kita/O semua/O ingin/O hidup/O damai/O di/O negeri/O ini/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/mXYMBb1YYf/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Bukan/O kegagalan/O yang/O mengakhiri/O karir/O kehidupan/O seorang/O anak/O manusia/O ,/O tapi/O menolak/O bangkit/O setelah/O jatuh/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
@aagym/O :/O Dibalik/O siapapun/O yang/O sukses/O pasti/O tersimpan/O sifat/O jujur/O dan/O dibalik/O siapapun/O yang/O rusak/O nama/O dan/O kemuliaannya/O pasti/O karena/O tak/O jujur/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O 3/O ./O Karena/O yg/O mencatut/O spt/O dlm/O rekaman/O tersebut/O adalah/O Ketua/O DPR/ORGANIZATION RI/ORGANIZATION ,/O yg/O dicatut/O Presiden-Wapres/O RI/ORGANIZATION ./O
@SyazwanRashdan/O :/O Bob/PERSON makan/O tak/O ajak/O apa/O ni/O ?/O !/O Padahal/O rumah/O aku/O dekat/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Selamat/O memperingati/O Maulid/O Nabi/O Muhammad/PERSON SAW/O https://t.co/0ya3VZRX8u/O
@infodishub/O :/O MENHUB/O :/O GROUNDBREAKING/O BANDARA/LOCATION AHMAD/LOCATION YANI/LOCATION RESPON/O dan/O ANTISIPASI/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION HADAPI/O PERTUMBUHAN/O PENUMPANG/O http://t.co/76UVMVH76T/O #BeritaPusat/O
@PersBirama/O :/O Besok/O ./O ./O !/O HIMPUNAN/ORGANIZATION MAHASISWA/ORGANIZATION Akuntansi/ORGANIZATION UNIKOM/ORGANIZATION "/O SEMINAR/O NASIONAL/O AKUNTANSI/O "/O
@DitaFridaBKS_/O :/O RT/O @IffahCY/O :/O besok/O gue/O tetep/O sekolah/O ./O
@KompasTV/O :/O RT/O @gracekarepu/O :/O Terimakasih/O @KompasTV/O sdh/O tayangin/O #AllEnglandSSP/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Terima/O kasih/O Kang/PERSON Oskar/PERSON ./O Membela/O aturan/O memang/O banyak/O resikonya/O ./O https://t.co/LiD9SGor2w/O
<45>https://t.co/ibvz2qOWoz/O Ngefans/O Berat,/O Ernest/PERSON Prakasa/PERSON Ajak/O Adinia/PERSON Wirasti/PERSON Main/O di/O '/O CTS/O '/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O kamu/O ikut/O pelatihan/O dagang/O aja/O ama/O pemkot/O bdg/LOCATION ./O trs/O ambil/O kredit/O Melati/O tanpa/O agunan/O sd/O 30/O jt/O ./O semangat/O !/O https://t.co/ezSkY3RwBB/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Ayo/O jadi/O saksi/O lahirnya/O juara/O !/O Nonton/O Putaran/O 2/O Yonex/ORGANIZATION All/O England/O pukul/O 19/O ./O 30/O WIB/O di/O KompasTV/ORGANIZATION #AllEnglandKompasTV/O https://t.co/2VUHDVYspc/O
<49>/O Begini/O Cara/O Mengolah/O Kulit/O Pisang/O Jadi/O Kerupuk/O https://t.co/HhCPcukPcZ/O
<91>/O Makna/O Kurban/O Idul/O Adha/O Bagi/O Jokowi/PERSON https://t.co/RJPX2z2ZkR/O https://t.co/aWeknwNv5D/O
@ThisIsHaqim/O :/O RT/O @ZahraSulaiman/O :/O Tengok/O sekolah/O semua/O
@makassar_tv/O :/O Mahasiswa/O yang/O berjumlah/O 40/O orang/O ini/O ,/O ditempatkan/O di/O tiga/O desa/O yang/O terletak/O di/O tiga/O kabupaten/O di/O Provinsi/O https://t.co/lSpBcbUo6d/O
@infomalang/O :/O @aanarianto3/O di/O pasar/LOCATION besar/LOCATION banyak/O
@KompasTV/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Debut/O Ahok/PERSON Maju/O Pilgub/O Secara/O Independen/O https://t.co/NcQshRFwFL/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Riam/O Jeram/O Pekalen/O (/O Bagian/O 1/O )/O https://t.co/cE30rDWPMm/O https://t.co/Pl84efBhv3/O
<30>/O Inzaghi/PERSON :/O Bayern/ORGANIZATION dan/O Juventus/ORGANIZATION Bertemu/O di/O Final/O Liga/O Champions/O ./O https://t/O .co/yGKLIDMOmi/O
@detikcom/O :/O Ngemil/O Makanan/O Ini/O di/O Malam/O Hari/O Bantu/O Lebih/O Cepat/O Tidur/O Nyenyak/O https://t.co/eHhAbqTiNk/O via/O @wolipop/O
@detikcom/O :/O Masih/O Terlalu/O Muda/O ,/O Model/O Remaja/O di/O Fashion/O Show/O Valentino/PERSON Jadi/O Kontroversi/O https://t.co/GfPVsSC95b/O via/O @wolipop/O https://t.co/s6MhQXRQ0U/O
@KabarBeritaa_/O :/O #News/O BNN/ORGANIZATION Ungkap/O Pabrik/O Sabu/O di/O Medan/LOCATION ,/O Empat/O Tersangka/O Dibekuk/O :/O Sebuah/O rumah/O yang/O dijadikan/O sebagai/O tempat/O https://t.co/JSp89lYd1l/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selamat/O tahun/O baru/O 2015/O ./O Banyak/O pelajaran/O yang/O didapat/O di/O tahun/O 2014/O untuk/O bangsa/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O Semoga/O tahun/O ini/O lebih/O baik/O lagi/O ./O
@Metro_TV/O :/O Tingkatkan/O Kualitas/O Layanan/O ,/O Prodia/O Tabanan/LOCATION Resmikan/O Gedung/O Baru/O https://t.co/B7X9bEZlbB/O
@Julialdi_87/O :/O RT/O @OngisnadeNet/O :/O Dan/O kemenangan/O Arema/ORGANIZATION jadi/O kado/O indah/O utk/O ulang/O tahun/O kota/O Malang/LOCATION #102NuhatKotaMalang/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @FPD_DPR/O :/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION Konsisten/O Tolak/O Revisi/O KPK/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/AK0942l42P/O
@jokowi/O :/O Tulisan/O netizen/O penting/O dalam/O menumbuhkan/O optimisme/O ,/O kejujuran/O dan/O etos/O kerja/O -/O Jkw/PERSON
@FrizkaAyunike/O :/O Bersama/O dosen/O akuntansi/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @MIsNgalamRaya/O :/O #TailNalim/O #SassuoloMILAN/O |/O Minggu/O 6/O //O 3/O //O 16/O ,/O 20/O ./O 00/O |/O @mbahkakongMLG/O (/O Jl/LOCATION ./O Kendalsari/LOCATION ,/O Suhat/LOCATION )/O |/O HTM/O 8K/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Bapak/O saya/O mengajarkan/O byk/O ,/O termasuk/O agar/O terus/O mengabdi/O utk/O negeri/O ./O Bagi/O saya/O ,/O beliau/O adl/O pahlawan/O ./O #HariPahlawan/O https://t.co/0bXI4fMJtq/O
@LadyKitari/O :/O Duh/O ,/O pak/O ./O ga/O ngerti/O sarkasme/O ?/O Sini/O saya/O ajarin/O !/O Atau/O kalo/O mau/O diajarin/O nyanyi/O lagu/O Indonesia/LOCATION Raya/O juga/O boleh/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O Di/O Yogyakarta/LOCATION ,/O #GMT9Mar16/O magnitudo/O gerhana/O saat/O puncak/O ,/O yaitu/O pukul/O 07/O :/O 23/O :/O 31/O ,/O 7/O WIB/O ,/O adalah/O 0/O ,/O 849/O
<94>/O Latih/O Persela/ORGANIZATION ,/O Aji/PERSON Santoso/PERSON Ajak/O Mustaqim/PERSON sebagai/O Asisten/O ./O https://t/O .co/y5gsrxPyFR/O
<43>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O Presiden/O Jokowi/PERSON :/O Kita/O Harus/O Tentukan/O “Core”/O Ekonomi/O Indonesia/LOCATION !/O https://t.co/S4dKxZGMmK/O https://t.co/cMqz6gqIoR/O
@detikcom/O :/O Penjelasan/O Blue/ORGANIZATION Bird/ORGANIZATION Terkait/O Ditangkapnya/O Feri/PERSON Yanto/PERSON karena/O Status/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION Provokasi/O https://t.co/BByQxL590Y/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Jangan/O terlalu/O sering/O mengulang/O cerita/O sukses/O masa/O lalu/O ,/O karena/O nanti/O orang/O mengira/O masa/O kini/O Anda/O kurang/O menghangatkan/O hati/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
@detikcom/O :/O 22/O Ribu/O Dokumen/O Anggota/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION Bocor/O ke/O Media/O Inggris/LOCATION https://t.co/UpzhG0v6p5/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @raswari1/O terima/O kasih/O mas/O doa/O dan/O dukungannya/O
@eddopaais/O :/O @iputribe/O Pa/O kabar/O ni/O ?/O Keluarga/O sehat/O ?/O Ya/O memang/O sdh/O lama/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Katakanlah/O Aamiin/O atau/O Retweet/O ,/O jika/O doa/O pagi/O ini/O adalah/O doa/O Anda/O juga/O ./O https://t.co/c5HdXXw9Zc/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O KTT/O Luar/O Biasa/O ke-5/O OKI/ORGANIZATION Organisasi/O Kerjasama/O Islam/O mengenai/O Palestina/LOCATION dan/O Al-Quds/O Al-Sharif/O https://t.co/Ga2weJGUla/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O 2/O ./O dan/O 9/O %/O pada/O thn/O 2016/O ./O Dengan/O harapan/O menggairahkan/O dunia/O usaha/O dan/O lapangan/O kerja/O ./O #munaskadin/O
@wxxyoung/O :/O jawa/LOCATION timur/LOCATION
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Produk/O Mebel/O Indonesia/LOCATION Masih/O Kalah/O Murah/O dari/O Vietnam/LOCATION https://t.co/P0Uli6EaGo/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Jokowi/PERSON :/O Jangan/O Sampai/O Ada/O Korban/O Lagi/O Masalah/O "/O Dwell/O Time/O "/O https://t.co/6wDy7VIKMj/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @pakdekarwo1950/O :/O Tahun/O 2014/O Pemkot/O minta/O ke/O saya/O agar/O jembatan/O diganti/O ,/O namun/O bukan/O soal/O teknis/O tapi/O soal/O estetika/O sehingga/O tidak/O saya/O
<54>/O Mau/O manggung/O bareng/O musisi/O idola?/O Yuk/O ikutan/O kontes/O #SuryanationQualityTime!/O Klik:/O https://t.co/lt4T5dyWj9/O https://t.co/7PRgKDLXLs/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O Rekayasa/O #Lalulintas/O di/O Bundaran/LOCATION Semeru/LOCATION &/O TL/O di/O pertigaan/O PLN/ORGANIZATION Jl/LOCATION ./O Basuki/LOCATION Rahmat/LOCATION ./O Pengguna/O jln/O harap/O menyesuaikan/O https://t.co/Tys6FYCwdx/O
@info_jogjakarta/O :/O RT/O @infojogjakarta/O :/O Hebat/O !/O Mereka/O Sukarela/O Keliling/O Yogya/LOCATION Hingga/O Dinihari/O untuk/O Perbaiki/O Jalan/O Berlubang/O https://t.co/EljS89Yh7r/O
@sagitancx/O :/O Hei/O @didietakarai/O @soldiweb/O yuk/O ikut/O @simulasisbmptn/O trbesar/O d/O indonesia/LOCATION ,/O serentak/O d/O 11/O kota/O https://t.co/KkezH5xf6y/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Selamatkan/O Anjing/O ,/O Wanita/O Berjilbab/O ini/O Tuai/O Pujian/O https://t.co/GYe3I7t4MC/O
<68>/O Ups/O ,/O iPhone/O 7/O Warna/O Jet/O Black/O Ternyata/O Rentan/O Kena/O Goresan/O https://t.co/tJXSK1F9RF/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O Acara/O silaturahmi/O tiga/O pilar/O ./O Sinergi/O Pemprov/O DKI/LOCATION bersama/O Polda/ORGANIZATION Metro/ORGANIZATION dan/O Kodam/ORGANIZATION Jaya/ORGANIZATION http://t.co/Go1HT2ayaH/O
<35>/O Surga/O Cantik/O Itu/O Terlihat/O Jelas/O dari/O Puncak/LOCATION Pulau/LOCATION Padar/LOCATION https://t/O .co/rTc4ZMU7W9/O https://t/O .co/U7d9pVFVut/O
@SURYAcoid/O :/O Kocak/O !/O Jelang/O Final/O Piala/O Bhayangkara/O 2016/O ,/O Wali/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION dan/O Bandung/LOCATION Sepakat/O Taruhan/O https://t.co/2wYpLb3ZfI/O https://t.co/xTeNns1zMT/O
<15>/O Ahok/PERSON Suruh/O Mantan/O Pengemudi/O yang/O Dipecat/O Minta/O Pesangon/O ke/O Trans/O Batavia/O ./O https://t/O .co/MPo5VYmZ4V/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Tantang/O Adrenalin/O Bersantap/O di/O Restoran/O Pinggir/O Tebing/O https://t.co/wfoTiJ6ZMD/O
<13>/O Egi/PERSON John/PERSON Tuduh/O Marshanda/PERSON Kena/O Penyakit/O Kelamin/O https://t.co/TqSKJPZMWI/O https://t.co/LHRRO6OPTp/O
<95>/O Dikabarkan/O Sudah/O Kembali/O Sehat/O ,/O Hillary/PERSON Clinton/PERSON Akan/O Lanjutkan/O Kampanye/O ./O https://t/O .co/pAt6GqJo3I/O
@aagym/O :/O Bila/O menasihati/O saudara/O seiman/O dengan/O hati/O yang/O penuh/O kejengkelan/O dan/O marah/O ,/O maka/O hasilnya/O adalah/O rasa/O sakit/O hati/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Ini/O saatnya/O menunjukkan/O kpd/O dunia/O bahwa/O Mahasiswa2/O Indonesia/LOCATION berperan/O aktif/O dlm/O aktifitas/O pendidikan/O multilateral/O https://t.co/ZJBitFhdkm/O
@infomalang/O :/O Hujan2/O enaknya/O makan/O bakso/O ./O ini/O salah/O satu/O bakso/O fave/O admin/O ,/O Bakso/O Kidul/LOCATION Pasar/LOCATION ./O Bakso/O https://t.co/JYpSVE6O8v/O
@detiksport/O :/O MU/ORGANIZATION XI/O :/O De/PERSON Gea/PERSON ,/O Darmian/PERSON ,/O Smalling/PERSON ,/O Blind/PERSON ,/O Rojo/PERSON ,/O Schneiderlin/PERSON ,/O Carrick/PERSON ,/O Lingard/PERSON ,/O Mata/PERSON ,/O Martial/PERSON ,/O Rashford/PERSON ./O
@ayu_yuliarizka/O :/O RT/O @celinedevinia/O :/O Ada/O yg/O ngerekam/O Blink/O di/O RTV/ORGANIZATION
@detiksport/O :/O Menyalip/O Rossi/PERSON ,/O Marquez/PERSON Berdoa/O Tak/O Lakukan/O Kesalahan/O https://t.co/bkeNPwjRBi/O
<54>/O 4/O Cara/O Memastikan/O Ayah/O Kandung/O Tanpa/O Tes/O DNA/O ./O https://t/O .co/F8ubvtoSef/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @pakdekarwo1950/O :/O Gambar/O kita/O kirim/O ke/O Ditjen/ORGANIZATION Jembatan/O Kementerian/O @KemenPU/O agar/O juga/O diteliti/O secara/O kualitas/O teknis/O Jembatan/O ./O */O Pakde/PERSON Karwo/PERSON
@kabarbisnis/O :/O Edwin/PERSON Hidayat/PERSON jadi/O wakil/O komisaris/O utama/O Pertamina/ORGANIZATION
<53>/O #News/O #ZonaMPR/O Penyuluh/O Pertanian/O Berharap/O Bantuan/O Ketua/O MPR/ORGANIZATION Agar/O Menjadi/O PNS/O https://t.co/BkoIwRbHeS/O https://t.co/zfzu6SaeGn/O
@jokowi/O :/O Setelah/O sekian/O lama/O ,/O Pak/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O Gubernur/O yang/O berhasil/O mewujudkan/O Masjid/LOCATION Fatahillah/LOCATION di/O Balai/LOCATION Kota/LOCATION DKI/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/2uEjPGMw7D/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 22/O :/O 28/O ,/O 5/O WIB/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Banda/LOCATION Aceh/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O ./O @unilubis/O memang/O betul/O cyber/O defense/O &/O drone/O telah/O saya/O rintis/O penerapannya/O ./O Khusus/O mengenai/O drone/O pernah/O saya/O coba/O di/O Papua/LOCATION dan/O tdk/O mudah/O ./O
@detiksport/O :/O Dukungan/O untuk/O Demichelis/PERSON Usai/O Tampil/O Buruk/O di/O Derby/O Manchester/LOCATION https://t.co/08xlKla9Ki/O https://t.co/1FhYOxTMJz/O
@SEPUTAR_EKONOMI/O :/O Mall/LOCATION Pondok/LOCATION Indah/LOCATION di/O Jakarta/LOCATION dibangun/O pada/O tahun/O 1991/O
@UndiknasDpm/O :/O Dewan/O Perwakilan/O Mahasiswa/O Pemerintahan/O Mahasiswa/O Universitas/ORGANIZATION Pendidikan/ORGANIZATION Nasional/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/2QYGLWwl26/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Smart/O City/O di/O kompleks/O Lido/O akn/O menjadi/O kawasan/O terintegrasi/O yg/O seluruhnya/O dikelola/O scr/O digital/O dgn/O teknologi/O tinggi/O https://t.co/WSYRZ47yDO/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Jangan/O lewatkan/O Putaran/O 2/O Yonex/ORGANIZATION All/O England/O di/O KompasTV/ORGANIZATION pukul/O 19/O ./O 30/O WIB/O dan/O ikuti/O juga/O kuisnya/O !/O #AllEnglandKompasTV/O https://t.co/53NcAGmEst/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O instagram/ORGANIZATION resmi/O saya/O hanya/O satu/O :/O basukibtp/O
@ghifariits/O :/O RT/O @GoBekasi/O :/O Polisi/ORGANIZATION Harapkan/O Masyarakat/O Semakin/O Berperan/O dalam/O Memberi/O Informasi/O
@jokowi/O :/O Karya/O Eko/PERSON Nugroho/PERSON jadi/O desain/O Louis/PERSON Vuitton/PERSON ./O Hebat/O ./O Seniman/O perlu/O dikoneksikan/O dengan/O industri/O fesyen/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/BVkpnuPGVg/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Om/O Mario/PERSON ,/O terkadang/O saya/O lihat/O tulisan/O CP/O di/O belakang/O gelar/O Master/O seseorang/O ./O itu/O artinya/O apa/O ?/O -/O Copy/O Paste/O ,/O mungkin/O ?/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Siapkan/O data/O bisnis/O Anda/O ./O Semua/O BISNIS/O BIDANG/O PERNIKAHAN/O bisa/O berpromosi/O di/O https://t.co/KBBfH4W6zZ/O ./O Pendaftaran/O akan/O segera/O dibuka/O ./O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Roberto/PERSON Mancini/PERSON Keluhkan/O Performa/O Gelandang/O Inter/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/fcTGGNj7PT/O
@Ismadew/O :/O AMSA/O Geriatri/O yang/O belum/O punah/O (/O Annisa/PERSON Ayu/PERSON ,/O Sunny/PERSON ,/O Green/LOCATION Leaf/LOCATION )/O
@prabowo/O :/O @TA_Amanda23/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION Terima/O kasih/O ./O Salam/O kembali/O untuk/O mbak/O Tiara/PERSON dan/O keluarga/O ./O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @PuspitaFM/O :/O #JMR/O Setelah/O dengar/O kabar/O tsb/O ,/O sang/O kakek/O langsung/O ditangani/O ,/O dan/O skrg/O di/O tempatkan/O di/O kwsn/O sukun/O ./O Bu/O Pipit/PERSON -/O Sekretaris/O
@Nissnissa__/O :/O Institut/ORGANIZATION Bisnis/ORGANIZATION dan/O Informatika/ORGANIZATION Kosgoro/LOCATION
@Hayatie_/O :/O RT/O @himpuncrtlawak/O :/O Bila/O kau/O balik/O rumah/O
<35>/O Cantik/O Mana/O ,/O Sheila/PERSON Marcia/PERSON Dulu/O atau/O Sekarang?/O https://t.co/EYOCmDMF5F/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @RendraFidza/O :/O Min/O info/O dong/O ,/O beli/O kalender/O yg/O lgsung/O sobek/O kayak/O gini/O di/O Malang/LOCATION ,/O dmana/O ya/O ?/O @infomalang/O https://t.co/kSlhOKpsAh/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Vaksin/O polio/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION semuanya/O diproduksi/O Bio/ORGANIZATION Farma/ORGANIZATION Bandung/LOCATION ./O Sudah/O teruji/O halal/O 100/O %/O ./O Tidak/O perlu/O khawatir/O ./O
@ShushLynn/O :/O RT/O @Tizznasuha/O :/O Aku/O 3/O bulan/O
@detikcom/O :/O Go-Jek/O Dilempari/O Batu/O oleh/O Sopir/O Taksi/O https://t.co/W3n6TpDdyD/O via/O @detik_foto/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Jari/O Sopir/O Blue/ORGANIZATION Bird/ORGANIZATION Putus/O Saat/O Bentrok/O Demo/O Tolak/O Uber/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/5wx1FAGt7O/O
@aagym/O :/O Silakan/O hadir/O nanti/O kajian/O doa/O nabi/O Yunus/PERSON agar/O lepas/O dari/O kesulitan/O yang/O berlapis/O dan/O amat/O menghimpit/O https://t.co/ynmod0cDj5/O
@detikcom/O :/O Sst/O ,/O Satu/O Lagi/O Tempat/O Keren/O di/O Yogyakarta/LOCATION https://t.co/1dR6YpZBsy/O via/O @detiktravel/O
<16>/O Guardiola/PERSON Tunggu/O Undangan/O Minum/O dari/O Mourinho/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/siooiGv1bh/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Nasdem/ORGANIZATION Dukung/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O Pertanda/O Partai/O Tak/O Pede/O https://t.co/WymGAxTlFB/O @basuki_btp/O
@Ivanfarianto/O :/O RT/O @BolaBanget/O :/O Penggawa/O Arema/ORGANIZATION Langsung/O Terbang/O ke/O Jakarta/LOCATION https://t.co/tfzVG3TLXO/O
@dkngardabangsa/O :/O RT/O @PKB_Surabaya/O :/O @KabilMubarak/O bersama/O kelompok/O budidaya/O ikan/O gotong/O royong/O mandiri/O kec-Sawahan/LOCATION @arifin_syam/O @BeritaPKB/O @FraksiPKB/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O KPUD/ORGANIZATION Minta/O Teman/O Ahok/PERSON Kawal/O Verifikasi/O KTP/O https://t.co/cAUKBTLAQg/O @basuki_btp/O
@jokowi/O :/O Industri/O adalah/O masa/O depan/O ekonomi/O kita/O ./O Kita/O harus/O memiliki/O daya/O saing/O tinggi/O supaya/O bisa/O berkompetisi/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/bi2IfUsTwi/O
@rc_candice/O :/O Saya/O kalau/O ga/O sayang/O sama/O agensi/O ini/O ,/O sayang/O sama/O membernya/O ,/O mungkin/O udah/O bener-bener/O ga/O ada/O ./O Asli/O ./O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Dirombak/O ,/O ini/O Direksi/O Baru/O BRI/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/xi4sCzwYKp/O
@infomalang/O :/O @TaMeritaMerita/O cc/O @dodotgiat/O
@rirismail_/O :/O RT/O @NabilFiq_/O :/O Kawan/O kawan/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Keluarga/O yang/O baik/O dimulai/O dengan/O cinta/O ,/O dibangun/O dengan/O kasih/O sayang/O ,/O dan/O dipelihara/O dengan/O kesetiaan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
<32>/O Pembalap/O Kursi/O Roda/O Ini/O Jadi/O Model/O Katalog/O Busana/O ./O https://t/O .co/rNBwsiQF08/O
<19>/O Daihatsu/ORGANIZATION Ekspor/O Sigra/O Pakai/O Lambang/O Toyota/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/Uo0UrGOBuP/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O RT/O @_DaengBaso/O :/O @infoBMKG/O Gerhana/O Matahari/O Makassar/LOCATION #MakassarGerhana2016/O #GMT2016/O cc/O :/O @DP_dannypomanto/O @iradiomakassar/O @Daeng_Info/O
@jchrisss/O :/O Surabaya/LOCATION Town/O Square/LOCATION (/O SUTOS/LOCATION )/O
@MonicaaTR_/O :/O RT/O @sittijulia27/O :/O sama/O keluarga/O
@detiksport/O :/O RT/O @AboutTheGame_/O :/O Aksi-aksi/O Bertahan/O Madrid/ORGANIZATION yang/O Mengalahkan/O Sevilla/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/26aWipTK3t/O
@aagym/O :/O Bismillah/O hari/O ini/O diluncurkan/O aplikasi/O Aa/O utk/O android/O silakan/O buka/O https://t.co/aamLqSvF4F/O https://t.co/9lOrtHvBXE/O
@CodSurabaya/O :/O Punya/O masalah/O dgn/O Masalah/O dgn/O Mata/O Minus/O ?/O Tiens/ORGANIZATION ada/O solusinya/O SMS/WA/O :/O 081333149409/O -/O PIN/O :/O 5CECF32B/O https://t.co/TDEhGOvSdL/O #Surabaya/O
<21>/O Ahok/PERSON :/O Kalau/O Sudah/O Terpidana/O ,/O Tidak/O Usah/O Ikut/O Pilkada/O https://t.co/2hkWa20XtR/O https://t.co/pB6dSNjR84/O
<16>/O Selamat/O Hari/O Pendidikan/O Nasional/O ,/O /O Mei/O 016/O ./O https://t.co/3rcMLNhrod/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O Simak/O #DialogInteraktif/O hari/O ini/O jam/O 11/O ./O 00/O ,/O tema/O Mmbangun/O Kota/O Kreatif/O ,/O narsum/O Kadisprindag/O di/O @RadioKencana/O FM/O 91/O ./O 9/O https://t.co/oaR0SpWrPX/O
<71>/O Peluncuran/O The/O Last/O Guardian/O Mundur/O Sampai/O Desember/O https://t/O .co/zetLYbOEha/O https://t/O .co/GwnfJjwkuK/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Ahok/PERSON :/O Sopir/O Taksi/O Cuma/O Diperalat/O dan/O Dibodohi/O Perusahaan/O https://t.co/GUF8gB6Bhe/O @basuki_btp/O https://t.co/mEPcCXDWN9/O
<32>/O Mensos/O Akan/O Tutup/O Lokalisasi/O di/O Seluruh/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/ngvcXwnT3f/O https://t.co/z10Z8dvTFG/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Masa/O Depan/O Plastik/O (/O Bagian/O 2/O )/O https://t.co/JO1jmWeoBH/O https://t.co/Kyz0rtELfc/O
@luluastarii/O :/O Gak/O di/O Jogja/LOCATION gak/O di/O Jakarta/LOCATION ketemu/O lo/O selalu/O di/O tempat/O makan/O ya/O (/O Shinta/PERSON @sushi_tei_indo/O )/O https://t.co/shLHLXkLsd/O
@detiksport/O :/O Djokovic/PERSON dan/O Kontroversi/O Kesetaraan/O Hadiah/O Uang/O Tenis/O Putra-Putri/O https://t.co/a4ZbUhVzWu/O
@infomalang/O :/O Founder/O #YOT/O @BillyBoen/O akan/O sharing/O kisah/O sukses/O di/O usia/O muda/O di/O #IMPACTMalang/O daftar/O https://t.co/GCfyHLyIcB/O https://t.co/7BVUPPgVc2/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O RT/O @saididu/O :/O #inilebihpenting/O RT/O @PrijantoRabbani/O :/O TNI/ORGANIZATION AD/ORGANIZATION Kembangkan/O 15/O Teknologi/O Alutsista/O Buatan/O Sendiri/O -/O Prijanto/PERSON Rabbani/PERSON
@charlies_jogja/O :/O RT/O @KutipanDAHSYAT/O :/O kesuksesan/O tidak/O datang/O begitu/O saja/O ,/O tetapi/O lahir/O dari/O kerja/O keras/O dan/O keyakinan/O untuk/O mewujudkannya/O menjadi/O kenyataan/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O salah/O satu/O jawaban/O terhadap/O Andre/PERSON Vltchek/PERSON yg/O mengritik/O kenapa/O Bandung/LOCATION terpilih/O Unesco/ORGANIZATION City/O of/O Design/O ./O https://t.co/yt2uMbOAmz/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Berpidato/O di/O Sidang/O PBB/ORGANIZATION http://t.co/ssM5iHLhGI/O
<88>/O Jokowi/PERSON Tinjau/O Latihan/O TNI/ORGANIZATION di/O Laut/LOCATION Jawa/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/VfPmxJhZqL/O
@detikcom/O :/O Cerita/O Pasien/O Diabetes/O Asal/O Indonesia/LOCATION Jalani/O Bypass/O Lambung/O di/O China/LOCATION https://t.co/U5VqYkE5XJ/O via/O @detikHealth/O
@prabowo/O :/O Siap/O !/O https://t.co/jpEuA2Npto/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Ketika/O saya/O berkunjung/O ke/O Bali/LOCATION Post/O ,/O saya/O melihat/O lukisan/O ini/O disalah/O satu/O sudut/O kantornya/O ./O http://t.co/Ut2rIpl9qO/O
@infomalang/O :/O @KarnawatiTP/O email/O dibalas/O jam/O dan/O hari/O kerja/O ya/O ,/O senin/O -/O jumat/O ,/O 09/O ./O 00/O -/O 17/O ./O 00/O wib/O :)/O
@detiksport/O :/O Sergio/PERSON Romero/PERSON Tolak/O Rumor/O River/ORGANIZATION Plate/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/m39Sy6kEa6/O https://t.co/bjYBTEXrSC/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Singgah/O di/O Angkringan/LOCATION Sejahtera/LOCATION ,/O UMKM/O binaan/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Kenjeran/LOCATION ./O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/rDAZA8j2gX/O
@detikcom/O :/O Kebakaran/O di/O Pesing/LOCATION Telah/O Padam/O ,/O KRL/O Tangerang/LOCATION -/O Jakarta/LOCATION Kembali/O Normal/O https://t.co/3CYNS7wQuB/O https://t.co/nzklqiR6kL/O
@detikcom/O :/O Dortmund/PERSON Tidak/O Merindukan/O Klopp/PERSON https://t.co/sRkuizlAgb/O via/O @detiksport/O https://t.co/kQ5IrNXzQt/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Jaga/O Kulit/O Cantik/O Anda/O dengan/O Kombinasi/O Susu/O Bubuk/O https://t.co/mvNq9jIqR3/O
@PrediksiRamalan/O :/O Pelajaran/O Cocok/O Untuk/O Cancer/O :/O Fisika/O ,/O B.Inggris/O ,/O Kimia/O ,/O Biologi/O ,/O Ekonomi/O ,/O Akuntansi/O ,/O Olahraga/O
@detikcom/O :/O Ahok/O :/O Perusahaan/O Taksi/O Tidak/O Tindak/O Sopir/O Anarkis/O ,/O Saya/O Juga/O Main/O Keras/O !/O https://t.co/LByXDPgAbH/O
@ronalkhairul/O :/O RT/O @bintangbete/O :/O Kalo/O liat/O berita/O di/O tv/O ,/O mau/O masalah/O politik/O ,/O ekonomi/O ataupun/O olahraga/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Bersama/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION Inc/ORGANIZATION dalam/O pelatihan/O marketing/O UMKM/O untuk/O menembus/O pasar/O MEA/ORGANIZATION Asean/ORGANIZATION ./O Mangprang/O !/O https://t.co/t7aeB0Lqt5/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O BNI/ORGANIZATION Bagi-bagi/O Dividen/O Rp2,26/O Triliun/O https://t.co/oHefgfJJdv/O
@Abigail_Sina/O :/O Hei/O @faliq_firdaus/O @SetiawanNoviq20/O yuk/O ikut/O @simulasisbmptn/O trbesar/O d/O indonesia/LOCATION ,/O serentak/O d/O 11/O kota/O https://t.co/0tXKzxiLcj/O
@detikcom/O :/O Sanitasi/O Lingkungan/O yang/O Baik/O Bantu/O Kurangi/O Jumlah/O Stunting/O https://t.co/QJp5IM9Qe9/O via/O @detikHealth/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Tujuh/O Manfaat/O Buah/O Merah/O bagi/O Kesehatan/O https://t.co/s1l0E0I9WJ/O
@Danta4ever/O :/O Adhek/PERSON ,/O Krisna/PERSON ,/O DE.Jon/PERSON Sekolah/ORGANIZATION Tinggi/ORGANIZATION Manajemen/ORGANIZATION Informatika/ORGANIZATION dan/O Teknik/ORGANIZATION Komputer/ORGANIZATION (/O STIKOM/ORGANIZATION )/O Bali/LOCATION
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Begini/O Cara/O Atasi/O Kulit/O Kering/O dan/O Kusam/O https://t.co/bjYMWYjmXp/O
@ichlbdch/O :/O @alexwang93/O aku/O akan/O hadir/O di/O kota/O kesayanganmu/O #iklan/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Anak/O muda/O yang/O menjadikan/O apa/O pun/O lebih/O diinginkan/O ,/O dibutuhkan/O ,/O dan/O dibeli/O SUKSES/O SEMUDA/O MUNGKIN/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
<4>/O Budi/PERSON Gunawan/PERSON Disarankan/O Pensiun/O Dini/O https://t/O .co/ctefBtrZ9E/O https://t/O .co/dhAfp5if0M/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O #GMT9Mar16/O di/O Banda/LOCATION Aceh/LOCATION akan/O teramati/O sejak/O Matahari/O terbit/O ,/O yaitu/O pukul/O 06/O :/O 48/O WIB/O hingga/O pukul/O 08/O :/O 24/O :/O 55/O ,/O 4/O WIB/O
@TiketMurah_Bali/O :/O #hotell/O #jalan2men/O hotel/O murah/O di/O bali/LOCATION 2015/O Bagai/O Rumah/O Bawah/O Ranah/O Yang/O Indah/O ,/O Seorang/O Pendiam/O Dan/O Culun/O Walau/O Den/O #hoteldiscount/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Terimakasih/O kepada/O seluruh/O kader/O Partai/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION yang/O telah/O bekerja/O keras/O ,/O di/O tengah/O badai/O yang/O melanda/O partai/O kita/O ./O http://t.co/NzpjxTZ8Mt/O
<33>/O Perjuangan/O RA/O Kartini/PERSON masih/O belum/O rampung/O ./O Dgn/O semangat/O "No/O Woman/O Left/O Behind"/O ,/O mari/O terus/O kita/O majukan/O kaum/O perempuan/O Indonesia/LOCATION ./O *SBY*/O
@detiksport/O :/O PR/O Conte/PERSON Masih/O Banyak/O untuk/O Euro/O 2016/O https://t.co/R1e2HmaBBK/O https://t.co/WaFncXMqmd/O
@alfand11/O :/O RT/O @OrenBarat/O :/O intinya/O sih/O 2/O kontestan/O final/O main/O di/O Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O biar/O seru/O ,/O rame/O ,/O kontoversial/O ,/O booming/O eventnya/O ./O seperti/O biasanya/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @bpbd_jatim/O :/O Prakiraan/O Cuaca/O di/O Wilayah/O Jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION pada/O hari/O Minggu/O -/O Senin/O ,/O 06/O -/O 07/O Maret/O 2016/O Pukul/O 07.00/O s/O //O d/O 07.00/O WIB/O #BMKG/O
@Metro_TV/O :/O Industri/O Kesehatan/O Jadi/O Target/O Utama/O Hacker/O di/O 2015/O https://t.co/V8Y1cpi41y/O
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O pernah/O menjadi/O minder/O dan/O tertekan/O dengan/O adanya/O cemoohan/O terhadap/O Islam/O ,/O karena/O bila/O mereka/O paham/O pasti/O akan/O suka/O Islam/O
<4>/O Kans/O Bacca/PERSON Pindah/O ke/O PSG/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/qlHdDcenQQ/O
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O hormat/O kepada/O pendonor/O darah/O hingga/O 100/O kali/O ./O Mereka/O pejuang/O kemanusiaan/O sejati/O ,/O patut/O dapat/O penghargaan/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/QXX64KMTEq/O
@infodishub/O :/O JEPANG/LOCATION TERTARIK/O PROYEK/O PEMBANGUNAN/O BANDARA/O ,/O PELABUHAN/O dan/O KERETA/O API/O CEPAT/O http://t.co/6Bx092hfQa/O #BeritaPusat/O
@prabowo/O :/O @NidaNur_F/O Alhamdulillah/O ,/O semoga/O mbak/O Nida/PERSON dan/O keluarga/O juga/O sehat/O selalu/O ./O
@BandungINFO_KU/O :/O Hadapi/O UNBK/O ,/O Sekolah/LOCATION Dipasangi/O Generator/O https://t.co/7UnMQZod8H/O https://t.co/qLbhWgLjKg/O
<16>/O Qualcomm/ORGANIZATION Buka/O Fasilitas/O Riset/O di/O Shanghai/LOCATION https://t/O .co/YocuQA0PYw/O https://t/O .co/fxoSv5bNSg/O
@e8irma/O :/O Kumpulan/O Foto/O Terbaru/O Artis/O Cantik/O Yuki/PERSON Kato/PERSON :/O https://t.co/rT59KY5syL/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @Mihrobi_KR/O :/O telah/O hilang/O dompet/O warna/O hitam/O a/O ./O n/O mihrobi/PERSON khalwatu/PERSON rihmi/PERSON ,/O bagi/O yg/O menemukan/O harap/O menghubungi/O 085236555589/O
<33>/O Fellaini/PERSON Siap/O Bayar/O Kepercayaan/O Mourinho/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/Vx9mQ6pwjJ/O
@KompasTV/O :/O PSG/ORGANIZATION Petik/O Usaha/O dan/O Kerja/O Keras/O Semusim/O https://t.co/Lg0uN4KDDG/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Penandatangan/O MoU/O MNC/ORGANIZATION Land/O bersama/O Kim/PERSON ,/O Byung-soo/PERSON ./O Jumat/O ,/O 11/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/q5YdeKHtxI/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @pakrwthemacz/O alhamdulillah/O sehat/O ,/O semoga/O bapak/O sehat/O juga/O ./O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Bersama/O Pak/O @jokowi/O melayat/O ke/O rumah/O duka/O Ibunda/O @pramonoanung/O https://t.co/sY7H37y4aT/O
@ganiarse/O :/O RT/O @daraprayoga_/O :/O Anggota/O DPR/ORGANIZATION yg/O artis/O ituh/O lg/O mau/O '/O kunjungan/O '/O ke/O Paris/LOCATION ./O Rakyat/O Indonesia/LOCATION baik/O ,/O bayarin/O pejabat/O keluar/O negeri/O terus/O ./O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @yusufxpratama/O :/O Kantor/O pusat/O JNE/ORGANIZATION di/O Jl/LOCATION ./O Hamid/LOCATION Rusdi/LOCATION Malang/LOCATION ,/O kira2/O buka/O sampai/O jam/O brapa/O ya/O ?/O @infomalang/O
@inpojabar/O :/O Harga/O Gabah/O di/O Kabupaten/O Cianjur/LOCATION Merosot/O Tajam/O ,/O Rp/O 3.700/O Per/O Kilogram/O -/O Tribun/O Jabar/LOCATION https://t.co/N48Z2kOtX3/O #Cianjur/O
@detiksport/O :/O Gusti/PERSON Randa/PERSON :/O yang/O Produk/O PSSI/ORGANIZATION itu/O 'kan/O ISL/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/JNXwpKULfD/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Terima/O kasih/O pada/O pak/O Bambang/PERSON Suryo/PERSON dan/O jajaran/O @KADIN_Indonesia/O sudah/O menerima/O saya/O dan/O memberi/O pencerahan/O ./O
@ShintaLasmaria/O :/O RT/O @Metro_TV/O :/O Sebelum/O Serahkan/O Data/O Transaksi/O ,/O BNI/ORGANIZATION Syariah/O Koordinasi/O dengan/O Asosiasi/O
<71>/O Gabung/O di/O https://t.co/sCWbIr8O6J/O dan/O dapatkan/O kesempatan/O u//O memenangkan/O 5/O Juta/O Rupiah/O ,/O Samsung/ORGANIZATION S7/O ,/O dan/O Samsung/ORGANIZATION A3/O https://t.co/swaju6wJO7/O
@prabowo/O :/O Aamiin/O ./O Terima/O kasih/O bung/O @ardywibawa/O
<33>/O Siap-Siap/O ./O ./O ./O Setelah/O Perseid/O Masih/O Ada/O Hujan/O Meteor/O Lagi!/O ./O https://t/O .co/FvJVK2XFgU/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @Pewedingtyasss/O :/O @infomalang/O Telah/O hilang/O STNK/O A/PERSON ./O N/PERSON Witanto/PERSON dengan/O Nomor/O polisi/O AG/O 3201/O JY/O bagi/O yang/O menemukan/O harap/O hubungi/O 085691911817/O
@HelmiAbdHalim/O :/O duduk/O sini/O rupanya/O rumah/O
@nuraeni_nenk/O :/O RT/O @Bukune/O :/O Untuk/O informasi/O pemesanan/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Ibu/O Mufidah/PERSON Kalla/PERSON meresmikan/O pelepasan/O ekspor/O bunga/O krisan/O pertama/O ke/O Jepang/LOCATION ./O @husainabdullah1/O https://t.co/HWMnvICwL0/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O BNI/ORGANIZATION Tak/O Ada/O Rencana/O Pungut/O Biaya/O Cek/O Saldo/O dan/O Tarik/O Tunai/O https://t.co/2qHEa9XGD8/O
@infojatim/O :/O Pasangan/O Bupati-Wabup/O Pacitan/LOCATION Terpilih/O akan/O Dilantik/O 4/O April/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Sudah/O waktunya/O Indonesia/LOCATION maju/O dalam/O pembangunan/O infrastruktur/O ./O https://t.co/2cJwgu5i6o/O
@radityadika/O :/O VLOG/O terbaru/O ,/O ngomongin/O waktu/O dapet/O piala/O kemarin/O di/O Indonesian/O Box/O Office/O Movie/O Awards/O ./O Tonton/O di/O sini/O :/O https://t.co/rpTbCuSCCe/O
@EventUniKLMFI/O :/O Esok/O juga/O akan/O berlangsung/O Program/O Gotong/O Royong/O anjuran/O JPKK/O ./O Dapat/O tshirt/O sponsor/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @adi_harmoko/O sipil/O atau/O militer/O sama/O baiknya/O ./O yang/O penting/O tulus/O untuk/O membangun/O bangsa/O ini/O ./O
@detikcom/O :/O Aura/O '/O Mistis/O '/O Saat/O Epilepsi/O Menyerang/O https://t.co/0LVZfW96jo/O via/O @detikHealth/O https://t.co/I52Da01C1H/O
@GalleryAceh/O :/O Boleh/O Buka/O Perusahaan/O di/O Luar/O Negeri/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Datuk/PERSON Seri/PERSON Tengku/PERSON Adnan/PERSON Bin/PERSON Tengku/PERSON Mansor/PERSON ,/O Kinabalu/LOCATION ,/O Sabtu/O 5/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/xDMkhqLEYq/O
@cubby_ghum/O :/O RT/O @posmetroinfo/O :/O Koto/LOCATION Sani/LOCATION Kabupaten/O Solok/LOCATION Diamuk/O Air/O Bah/O ,/O 2000/O Warga/O Menyelamatkan/O Diri/O ./O https://t.co/ioMTkcgTsR/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Aspirasi/O rakyat/O (/O yg/O muncul/O dlm/O Tour/O de/O Java/O SBY/PERSON )/O bukan/O utk/O dihancurkan/O ,/O justru/O harus/O didengar/O ./O Bukankah/O pemimpin/O mesti/O
@detiksport/O :/O RT/O @AboutTheGame_/O :/O Ini/O namanya/O ./O ./O ./O Sudah/O jatuh/O dipotret/O suporter/O lawan/O juga/O :/O D/O https://t.co/SpxQxMalLJ/O
@radityadika/O :/O Hmmmm/O ./O ./O https://t.co/agPVmym1e2/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SartonoHutomo/O :/O @SBYudhoyono/O @Edhie_Baskoro/O @PDemokrat/O https://t.co/8LwnreuEAs/O
<84>/O The/ORGANIZATION Virgin/ORGANIZATION Berkurban/O di/O Daerah/O Bekas/O Banjir/O Bandang/LOCATION https://t.co/9UWdjtIrC9/O https://t.co/K2d4NCATOr/O
<23>/O Buat/O yang/O di/O Surabaya/PERSON ,/O Palembang/PERSON ,/O Medan/PERSON ,/O Makassar/PERSON ,/O Yuk/O ikutan/O #SuryanationQualityTime/O Klik:/O https://t.co/lt4T5dyWj9/O https://t.co/7PRgKDLXLs/O
@seputar_sumbar/O :/O Peringatan/O Dini/O Cuaca/O Wilayah/O JABODETABEK/LOCATION
@prabowo/O :/O Insya/O Allah/O ,/O @engkong91/O ./O Saya/O mohon/O doa/O saudara/O selalu/O untuk/O Koalisi/ORGANIZATION Merah/ORGANIZATION Putih/ORGANIZATION ./O Ancaman/O kepada/O bangsa/O kita/O nyata/O ,/O dan/O harus/O kita/O hadapi/O ./O
@bumi_sikerei/O :/O Nasrul/PERSON Abit/PERSON menyatakan/O siap/O bantu/O Kabupaten/O Kepulauan/LOCATION Mentawai/LOCATION kelola/O destinasi/O wisata/O https://t.co/cnUy8LM0Nz/O
@HendraJonathanT/O :/O RT/O @GreatestTweet/O :/O Pendidikan/O tidak/O bisa/O membuat/O semua/O jadi/O pemimpin/O
@DaerahSurabaya/O :/O Disnaker/ORGANIZATION Surabaya/LOCATION :/O PT/ORGANIZATION Pelindo/ORGANIZATION III/ORGANIZATION Terbukti/O Melanggar/O Aturan/O Ketenagakerjaan/O https://t.co/w3WDYZARbY/O
<95>/O Hari/O Kunjung/O Perpustakaan/O ,/O Upaya/O Dongkrak/O Minat/O Baca/O Masyarakat/O https://t/O .co/VNEyWuucqk/O https://t/O .co/fS2VW4Ng0B/O
@Kota_Solok/O :/O Bagi/O berita/O ,/O informasi/O ,/O
@prabowo/O :/O Inna/O Lillahi/O wa/O inna/O ilaihi/O raji/O 'un/O ./O Saya/O dan/O Partai/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION turut/O berduka/O atas/O kepergian/O bapak/O Ben/PERSON Mboi/PERSON ,/O pengayom/O masyarakat/O NTT/LOCATION ./O
@prabowo/O :/O Insya/O Allah/O ./O http://t.co/Ka0gNlpW37/O
@DoodleCSH/O :/O Cinta/O itu/O tidak/O selalu/O menuntut/O kesempurnaan/O ./O Cinta/O itu/O ketika/O kita/O dapat/O menutupi/O kekurangan/O seseorang/O dalam/O kebersamaan/O ./O
<37>/O SBY/PERSON bicara/O ttg/O sengketa/O Laut/LOCATION Tiongkok/LOCATION Selatan/LOCATION ,/O dan/O sampaikan/O posisi/O &/O kepentingan/O Indonesia/LOCATION ,/O juga/O sbg/O anggota/O dan/O negara/O terbesar/O di/O ASEAN/ORGANIZATION ./O
<91>/O Gabigol/O Bawa/O "Pengawal"/O ke/O Inter/O ./O https://t/O .co/lo2EYvnyTC/O
@zwnishhrddn/O :/O RT/O @SyedSaddiq/O :/O Dah/O tahu/O tahap/O pendidikan/O rendah/O ,/O kenapa/O potong/O pendidikan/O ?/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Pembukaan/O KTT/O Pembangunan/O Berkelanjutan/O 2015/O di/O Markas/LOCATION Besar/LOCATION PBB/ORGANIZATION ,/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION ,/O Amerika/LOCATION Serikat/LOCATION http://t.co/4oLnL8xXTo/O http://t.co/mtc87gFsL5/O
@detikcom/O :/O Berbalas/O Surat/O ,/O Menpora/O Rahasiakan/O Pendekatan/O ke/O FIFA/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/xaQekN3G2V/O via/O @detiksport/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Tantang/O Ahok/PERSON ,/O Lulung/PERSON Juga/O Mau/O Jadi/O Gubernur/O Lewat/O Independen/O https://t.co/aIIjmkZAOB/O @basuki_btp/O
<75>https://t.co/lgidQ6fmbe/O Inilah/O Cowok/O Ganteng/O Yang/O Jadi/O Inspirasi/O Album/O Kedua/O Shawn/PERSON Mendes/PERSON
@Amaliapsptdw/O :/O Malam/O Puncak/O Pekan/O Raya/O Akuntansi/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Ada/O orang/O yang/O hanya/O ingin/O bekerja/O digaji/O ,/O yang/O naik/O atau/O tidaknya/O diserahkan/O kepada/O keputusan/O orang/O lain/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
<34>/O 5/O Hotel/LOCATION Kolam/O Terindah/O yang/O Pernah/O Ada/O di/O Dunia/O https://t.co/EughgU9vFO/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @dir1ku/O :/O Foto/O bersama/O setelah/O dialog/O Ttg/O Permasalahan/O #Disabilitas/O #HWDI/O #AulaSkodam/O @pemkotmalang/O @MalangKab/O https://t.co/rUe4f42LHc/O
@rskyamaliaa/O :/O Kok/O gatau/O diri/O yaa/O sekalinya/O ngumpul/O gainget/O pulang/O ?/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Orang/O yang/O melakukan/O kebaikan/O mungkin/O belum/O menerima/O kebaikan/O ,/O tapi/O sudah/O dijauhkan/O dari/O keburukan/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
@AnjasPlystr/O :/O @pln_123/O halo/O pln/O ,/O Kota/O Kendal/LOCATION jawa/LOCATION tengah/LOCATION listrik/O padam/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Lindsay/PERSON Lohan/PERSON Pernah/O Tolak/O Ajakan/O Bercinta/O Harry/PERSON Styles/PERSON https://t.co/ewkLmiGqjo/O
@Juwita_DP/O :/O Nemenin/O para/O wanita/O ldr/O ,/O hahaha/O
@InfoSULUT_/O :/O Boham/PERSON :/O MaMa/O Telah/O Menjadi/O Milik/O Semua/O Masyarakat/O Kota/O Bitung/LOCATION -/O Manado/LOCATION https://t.co/HlTIZph8mc/O #Bitung/O
@jokowi/O :/O Kedatangan/O kapal/O ternak/O perdana/O ,/O angkut/O sapi/O dari/O NTT/LOCATION ke/O Jakarta/LOCATION ./O Ongkos/O kirim/O efisien/O ,/O daging/O sapi/O lebih/O murah/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/pdySuyqwkz/O
@suaranusa/O :/O Malang/LOCATION Resmi/O Gelar/O Pameran/O Kota/O Kreatif/O https://t.co/YVmnT7et4U/O
@InfoMalangCity/O :/O Disnaker/ORGANIZATION Surabaya/LOCATION :/O PT/ORGANIZATION Pelindo/ORGANIZATION III/ORGANIZATION Terbukti/O Melanggar/O Aturan/O Ketenagakerjaan/O https://t.co/OBdFcILx8R/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O para/O santri/O Pondok/ORGANIZATION Pesantren/ORGANIZATION Al/ORGANIZATION Falah/ORGANIZATION ,/O Landasan/LOCATION Ulin/LOCATION ,/O Banjarbaru/LOCATION ,/O Kalimantan/LOCATION Selatan/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 3/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/PjET56dqHe/O
@radityadika/O :/O Waduh/O ./O ./O https://t.co/QuDg2giOvK/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O RT/O @PRFMnews/O :/O Hari/O ini/O PKL/O di/O Jalan/LOCATION Purnawarman/LOCATION Akan/O Direlokasi/O https://t.co/4dwa8s90sM/O https://t.co/UeCep463I4/O
@detikcom/O :/O Jokowi/PERSON Tinjau/O Pos/O Perbatasan/O RI/LOCATION -/O Malaysia/LOCATION di/O Entikong/LOCATION https://t.co/yofOwT5xJp/O
<91>/O Debutan/O Liga/O Champions/O ,/O Leicester/ORGANIZATION Ingin/O Ikut/O Jejak/O Nottingham/ORGANIZATION Forest/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/15TDaG5gBb/O
@jokowi/O :/O Perundungan/O ,/O kekerasan/O pada/O anak/O tidak/O bisa/O ditolerir/O ./O Orangtua/O ,/O pendidik/O dan/O media/O ujung/O tombak/O perlindungan/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/QxjXJSX8uv/O
<14>/O De/PERSON Bruyne/PERSON Tak/O Khawatirkan/O Absennya/O Aguero/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/quZZU6qaE5/O
@lifiamonica/O :/O RT/O @DreamersRadioID/O :/O Tak/O Perlu/O Khawatir/O Meninggalkan/O Ikan/O Peliharaan/O di/O Rumah/LOCATION ,/O Tas/O Ini/O Dapat/O Dijadikan/O Akuarium/O https://t.co/AQAZsEwSzx/O
@iljc12/O :/O Keluarga/O yang/O baik/O dimulai/O dengan/O cinta/O ,/O dibangun/O dengan/O kasih/O sayang/O ,/O dan/O dipelihara/O dengan/O kesetiaan/O ./O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O Info/O lengkap/O dari/O @infoBMKG/O ttg/O kota-kota/O yg/O dimungkinkan/O terlihat/O #GerhanaMatahari/O 9/O Maret/O 2016/O dpt/O diunduh/O di/O https://t.co/TY1h24SKq2/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O Karena/O itu/O jika/O ada/O prostitusi/O terselubung/O ./O Yuk/O masyarakat/O laporkan/O ke/O pihak/O berwenang/O ./O udah/O merusak/O moral/O ,/O ilegal/O pula/O
@RioHaryanto_F1/O :/O RT/O @PTPERTAMINA/O :/O Jelang/O GP/O Bahrain/LOCATION ada/O kuis/O loh/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Ini/O Alasan/O Putri/O Raja/O Thailand/LOCATION Menyaksikan/O GMT/O di/O Ternate/LOCATION https://t.co/A5dJcPkzon/O
@jjkurs/O :/O Kangen/O yang/O lain/O tp/O males/O manggil/O nick/PERSON ./O Entar/O dikira/O absen/O sekolah/O ./O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Riam/O Jeram/O Pekalen/O (/O Bagian/O 2/O )/O https://t.co/EJ2QMLV7q8/O https://t.co/9ONtkFtrdf/O
@detikcom/O :/O Begini/O Gaya/O Laskar/O Gerhana/O Bidik/O GMT/O https://t.co/m2GjrtOpXw/O via/O @detik_foto/O
<53>/O Kemenangan/O di/O Kiev/LOCATION ,/O Kado/O Ulang/O Tahun/O Sang/O Istri/O ./O https://t/O .co/AAXwY3dvAm/O ./O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @KelSawojajar/O :/O Ayo/O jangan/O bosan/O ker/O ./O bikin/O lingkungan/O kita/O bersih/O dan/O nyaman/O @pemkotmalang/O https://t.co/3m6ZqqQzCo/O
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O harap/O kita/O semua/O bekerja/O saja/O dengan/O baik/O ./O Urusan/O angkat/O dan/O ganti/O menteri/O biar/O jadi/O urusan/O saya/O -/O Jkw/PERSON
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Untuk/O di/O darat/O ,/O jalur/O kereta/O harus/O ditambah/O ./O Selain/O lebih/O cepat/O dan/O aman/O dalam/O mengangkut/O barang/O ,/O juga/O mengurangi/O kemacetan/O di/O jalan/LOCATION ./O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Jadi/O Saksi/O Zaskia/PERSON Gotik/PERSON ,/O Syahnaz/PERSON Diberondong/O 18/O Pertanyaan/O https://t.co/ig7L5Ky3X2/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Tahun/O ini/O KPK/ORGANIZATION Fokus/O Perbaiki/O Tata/O Kelola/O Pangan/O https://t.co/ceLi9k2uKe/O
@pazira_nora/O :/O RT/O @hazifah25/O :/O tnpa/O kita/O sadari/O koruptor/O itu/O orng2/O yang/O berada/O pada/O ekonomi/O tinggi/O
@jokowi/O :/O Ayo/O berikan/O ide/O ,/O bagaimana/O supaya/O orang/O memiliki/O kesadaran/O tidak/O mengotori/O lingkungan/O kita/O -/O Jkw/PERSON
@banditzz69/O :/O maleh/O gak/O ngerti/O lapo/O roy/PERSON suryo/PERSON dadi/O trend/O ,/O opo/O wes/O hafal/O lagu/O Indonesia/LOCATION Raya/O ?/O
@infodishub/O :/O PENUMPANG/O DAPAT/O KOMPENSASI/O JIKA/O KERETA/O TERLAMBAT/O http://t.co/8BXJ410YfG/O #BeritaPusat/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Prabowo/PERSON Sebut/O Kunjungan/O ke/O Kantor/LOCATION Luhut/PERSON Hanya/O Silaturahmi/O https://t.co/Hwp8pSsLyo/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @19fe87/O :/O @infomalang/O sabit/O matahari/O nya/O https://t.co/8QfIfRzNZm/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Ferdinand/PERSON Desak/O Klub/O Premier/O League/O Rekrut/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON https://t.co/KM9l24Vn1v/O
@detikcom/O :/O Video/O Turis/O China/LOCATION Serakah/O Ambil/O Menu/O Buffet/O Beredar/O di/O Dunia/LOCATION Maya/O https://t.co/9fbVQ6QF0h/O via/O @detikfood/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Menjelang/O magrib/O ./O Biar/O hari/O libur/O semoga/O tidak/O lupa/O sholat/O ya/O ,/O teman-teman/O ./O Selamat/O menunaikan/O ibadah/O sholat/O magrib/O dan/O selamat/O berlibur/O ./O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O #InfoBencana/O Sabtu/O (/O 27/O //O 2/O )/O 06.00/O WIB/O longsor/O di/O wil/O Kel/LOCATION Tanjungrejo/LOCATION Sukun/LOCATION ,/O korban/O nihil/O ./O Lokasi/O diberi/O grs/O bahaya/O https://t.co/B3juLmhSuQ/O
@paradization/O :/O Prospek/O Kerja/O Jurusan/O Teknik/O Informatika/O
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O segera/O panggil/O Menhub/O ./O Ojek/O dibutuhkan/O rakyat/O ./O Jangan/O karena/O aturan/O rakyat/O jadi/O susah/O ./O Harusnya/O ditata/O -/O Jkw/PERSON
@infodishub/O :/O PENDAFTARAN/O ANGKUTAN/O GRATIS/O SEPEDA/O MOTOR/O DENGAN/O KA/O DIPERPANJANG/O http://t.co/sUBXDlrFpd/O #BeritaPusat/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Turut/O berbelasungkawa/O atas/O wafatnya/O bpk/O Soegeng/PERSON Sarjadi/PERSON ./O Semoga/O amal/O ibadahnya/O diterima/O yang/O Maha/O Kuasa/O ./O
@damima_may/O :/O RT/O @ipphoright/O :/O Istri/O nggak/O minta/O macem2/O ./O Dia/O hanya/O perlu/O kasih/O sayang/O
@BSI_DewiSartika/O :/O RT/O @KuliahBSIAja/O :/O Sobat/O BSI/ORGANIZATION ,/O Berikut/O ini/O adalah/O salah/O satu/O alumni/O BSI/ORGANIZATION yg/O sukses/O mengikuti/O program/O
<80>/O Juventus/ORGANIZATION Dilarang/O Terbuai/O oleh/O Pujian/O ./O https://t/O .co/LvwqjehsE3/O
@khAndreSalim/O :/O 4/O April/O 2016/O Lawang/LOCATION Sewu/LOCATION Semarang/LOCATION ,/O Jawa/LOCATION Tengah/LOCATION https://t.co/vhfrPHPv0g/O
@infodishub/O :/O JERMAN/LOCATION DUKUNG/O INDONESIA/LOCATION DALAM/O PROGRAM/O PENURUNAN/O GAS/O EMISI/O KENDARAAN/O http://t.co/gHf48xoej0/O #BeritaPusat/O
@detikcom/O :/O Video/O Sopir/O Taksi/O Tabrak/O Pendemo/O yang/O Men-sweepingnya/O https://t.co/gKTSk2U8W4/O via/O @detik_tv/O
@detikcom/O :/O #MostPopular/O Gadis/O Pemanis/O Beraksi/O di/O Bangkok/LOCATION Motor/O Show/O 2016/O https://t.co/QMlotZoRyc/O via/O @detikOto/O https://t.co/vthhx0Ippa/O
@RealtyRumah/O :/O Rumah/O Dijual/O di/O Sidoarjo/LOCATION jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION
@Sari_Dewi178/O :/O Karawang/LOCATION pastikan/O tarif/O angkutan/O umum/O turun/O
@prabowo/O :/O Mari/O kawal/O hitungan/O suara/O di/O setiap/O TPS/O ,/O kecamatan/O ,/O kabupaten/O ,/O provinsi/O sampai/O ke/O selesainya/O penghitungan/O &/O penetapan/O resmi/O di/O KPU/ORGANIZATION Pusat/O ./O
@basuki_btp/O :/O RT/O @DinasTA_Jakarta/O :/O Keg/O Penanganan/O saluran/O diperempatan/O joglo/O Kec/O Kembangan/LOCATION @PoskoDPUDKI/O @TMCPoldaMetro/O http://t.co/H8lvbuehhn/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O RT/O @kompascom/O :/O Ridwan/PERSON Kamil/PERSON Minta/O Pengusaha/O Tak/O Ambil/O Untung/O dari/O Penjualan/O Kantong/O Plastik/O https://t.co/YaaEKZZEVc/O
@citycityzens/O :/O Dewasa/O tak/O selalu/O menuntut/O kita/O berubah/O ,/O tapi/O perubahan/O yang/O baik/O selalu/O menuntut/O kita/O tuk/O lebih/O dewasa/O ./O
@KompasTV/O :/O 2/O pekan/O setelah/O dikeluarkan/O dari/O sejumlah/O gorong-gorong/O di/O Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O sampah/O kabel/O menumpuk/O di/O wilayah/O Benhill/LOCATION ./O #KompasPagi/O pkl/O 04/O ./O 30/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Bedah/O Statistik/O ,/O 4/O Bukti/O Peningkatan/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION bersama/O Juergen/PERSON Klopp/PERSON https://t.co/doEJ5ceQCN/O
@detiksport/O :/O Tantangan/O PB/O Djarum/ORGANIZATION untuk/O PBSI/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/5x95Si1qbI/O
<78>https://t.co/GDfwUVHFHw/O [VIDEO]/O Maia/PERSON Estianty/PERSON Beberkan/O Aktivitas/O Al/PERSON El/PERSON Dul/PERSON Saat/O di/O Rumah/LOCATION
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Karena/O pertama/O kali/O ,/O ada/O perasaan/O deg/O degan/O saat/O ke/O bilik/O suara/O ./O Saya/O berhati-hati/O ./O Jgn/O sampai/O suara/O saya/O ,/O krn/O tak/O paham/O ,/O malah/O jd/O tak/O sah/O ./O
<44>/O Hasil/O Liga/O Champions/O ,/O 3/O September/O 016/O ./O https://t/O .co/l11ue9FGWD/O
@ndhirariffn/O :/O Berbahagia/O lah/O kalian/O yang/O berada/O di/O rumah/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O Bupati/O Purbalingga/LOCATION Bpk/O Tasdi/PERSON ./O Bupati/O yang/O didukung/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION pada/O saat/O pemilihan/O lalu/O ./O Rabu/O 16/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/LcdGVp5Kjo/O
<9>/O 5/O Fakta/O Menarik/O Jelang/O Barcelona/ORGANIZATION Vs/O Celtic/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/rZH6SHD709/O https://t.co/bTP9kK5lSF/O
@detiksport/O :/O Southampton/ORGANIZATION Perpendek/O Ketinggalan/O dari/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION di/O Babak/O Kedua/O https://t.co/r2EPF3g0yp/O
@Ariwidodo76/O :/O RT/O @infoBMKG/O :/O #Gempa/O 204/O km/O TimurLaut/LOCATION KEP-TALAUD/LOCATION -/O SULUT/LOCATION
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @GPRindonesia/O :/O Yuk/O ,/O simak/O dialog/O #KTTLuarBiasaOKI/O jam/O 5/O sore/O ini/O hanya/O di/O @RRI/O Pro/O 3/O FM/O 88/O ./O 8/O atau/O streaming/O di/O https://t.co/ggi78cjqJu/O
@prabowo/O :/O @Sei_Ko_Ki/O @dinotsss/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION Setuju/O ./O
<27>/O Jika/O manajemen/O mencintai/O &/O perhatikan/O kesejahteraan/O buruh/O ,/O &/O buruh/O disiplin/O ,/O produktif/O &/O cintai/O perusahaannya/O ,/O semuanya/O menang/O ./O *SBY*/O
@Metro_TV/O :/O Sejumlah/O Advokat/O Deklarasikan/O APDI/O https://t.co/bJCuyJTgg4/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Bela/O Timnas/O ,/O Bintang/O Arsenal/ORGANIZATION Keracunan/O Makanan/O https://t.co/8H2B5qZeEy/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bersama/O kader-kader/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Kenjeran/LOCATION ./O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/VQdAiS1fOr/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Produk/O Solar/O Baru/O Diluncurkan/O Tahun/O ini/O https://t.co/e1BDLD049c/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O 07/O :/O 21/O :/O 33/O ,/O 0/O WIB/O :/O Puncak/O Gerhana/O di/O Jakarta/LOCATION #GMT9Mar16/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O Selamat/O siang/O ,/O udah/O lama/O saya/O nggak/O ngetwit/O ./O Sambil/O di/O perjalanan/O mau/O twit/O beberapa/O hal/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O di/O Jayapura/LOCATION ,/O #GMT9Mar16/O akan/O teramati/O sejak/O pukul/O 08/O :/O 53/O :/O/O 42/O ,/O 8/O WIT/O hingga/O pukul/O 11/O :/O 48/O :/O 45/O ,/O 9/O WIT/O
@ferry_rinaldi/O :/O Solusi/O Cerdas/O DJP/O atasi/O Online/O Error/O
@bambangelf/O :/O RT/O @Amal_Alghozali/O :/O Setiap/O baser/O dapat/O satu/O unit/O rumah/O //O apartrmen/O https://t.co/ilkQH57aSK/O
@aagym/O :/O Khotbah/O Jumat/O di/O festival/O KPK/ORGANIZATION ,/O diskusi/O agar/O bangun/O generasi/O muda/O anti/O korupsi/O ,/O ada/O yang/O minat/O gabung/O ?/O https://t.co/tHysOqqwgK/O
@prabowo/O :/O @Tjahaja_Timoer/O Terima/O kasih/O ./O Sama-sama/O bung/O Timoer/PERSON ./O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Selamat/O pagi/O Indonesia/LOCATION ,/O Salam/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION !/O Persiapan/O tour/O De/O Java/O bersama/O @SBYudhoyono/O "/O untuk/O Rakyat/O ,/O Demokrat/ORGANIZATION Peduli/O &/O Menyerap/O Aspirasi/O "/O ./O ./O ./O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Selamat/O hari/O raya/O Nyepi/O Tahun/O baru/O Saka/O 1938/O https://t.co/mJSAiL0HcM/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Cara/O Yakinkan/O Orangtua/O bagi/O Anda/O yang/O Ingin/O Nikah/O Muda/O https://t.co/Cx9uXiQjlH/O
@basuki_btp/O :/O Hidup/O bermasyarakat/O itu/O ada/O aturannya/O ./O Demi/O ketertiban/O dan/O kenyamanan/O kita/O semua/O ./O Jangan/O cuma/O mau/O enak/O sendiri/O
@prabowo/O :/O @jannah_eels/O Walaikumsalam/O ./O Terima/O kasih/O ./O Semoga/O Siti/PERSON dan/O keluarga/O juga/O mendapat/O kelancaran/O dalam/O berpuasa/O ./O Salam/O untuk/O teman-teman/O ./O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @KelSawojajar/O :/O TEMU/O WARGA/O Rajajowas/O Tahes/O Komes/O ,/O Minggu/O 28-2-2016/O ,/O pukul/O 10.00/O WIB/O @pemkotmalang/O @infomalangraya/O @lnfomalang/O
@Melodiest48/O :/O RT/O @DeviFP/O :/O Subsidi/O cd/O Mahagita/O DS/O Jogja/LOCATION 24/O April/O 2016/O Jogja/LOCATION City/LOCATION Mall/LOCATION !/O https://t.co/Cq5EFlV78J/O
@detikcom/O :/O PDIP/ORGANIZATION Siapkan/O Ganjar/PERSON dan/O Risma/PERSON ke/O Pilgub/O DKI/LOCATION ,/O Ahok/PERSON :/O Gua/O Nggak/O Masalah/O https://t.co/pGoHAUToys/O
@aagym/O :/O Ternyata/O Starbucks/O nyata/O sekali/O mendukung/O dan/O penyumbang/O LGBT/O ,/O setiap/O cangkir/O jadi/O ikut/O jadi/O donatur/O https://t.co/xaVLcgvbKJ/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @SBYudhoyono/O :/O Jadi/O ,/O tinggal/O melaksanakan/O kan/O ?/O Selamat/O Hari/O Pers/O Nasional/O 9/O Februari/O 2016/O ./O Jayalah/O pers/O Indonesia/LOCATION -/O merdeka/O ,/O berani/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O [/O VIDEO/O ]/O Para/O Polisi/O Gendut/O ini/O Diberikan/O Sanksi/O https://t.co/tK3fYjtub7/O https://t.co/JM0g3Q4K67/O
@deassyratnasari/O :/O @CommuterLine/O :/O Slmt/O Mlm/O ./O Informasi/O kereta/O dari/O manggarai/LOCATION ke/O bogor/LOCATION apakah/O sudah/O berjalan/O ?/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Mungkin/O tidak/O ada/O rasa/O sepi/O yang/O lebih/O membaperkan/O daripada/O menjadi/O single/O yang/O tidak/O bergaul/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON -/O https://t.co/KBBfH4W6zZ/O
@detiksport/O :/O '/O Juve/O Luapkan/O Kekecewaan/O Tersingkir/O di/O Liga/O Champions/O dengan/O Cara/O Positif/O '/O https://t.co/Pw2APtU77E/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O tiap/O hari/O kang/O ./O wayahna/O ./O https://t.co/cPEZVXqHKN/O
@prabowo/O :/O @putroMuhammad/O Selamat/O ulang/O tahun/O ,/O Putro/PERSON ./O Semoga/O terus/O diberikan/O kesehatan/O dan/O akal/O untuk/O berbakti/O pada/O orang/O tua/O dan/O bangsa/O negara/O ./O
<44>/O RT/O @NetNews_MetroTV:/O Seperti/O ini/O wajah/O Terminal/LOCATION Petikemas/LOCATION Kalibaru/LOCATION Tanjung/LOCATION Priok/LOCATION https://t/O .co/0KpB79Zd2s/O @kemenhub151/O @Metro_TV/O https://t/O .c…/O
@infodishub/O :/O KEMENHUB/ORGANIZATION ANGKUT/O 6/O ./O 300/O MOTOR/O GRATIS/O DENGAN/O KA/O http://t.co/vBAG3CaLUA/O #BeritaPusat/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Ibu/O Datin/PERSON Seri/PERSON Anggraini/PERSON dan/O putrinya/O Nadira/PERSON Adnan/PERSON di/O MNC/ORGANIZATION Tower/O ./O Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O Jumat/O 11/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/BfaUdlvTdz/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Mau/O dapat/O iPod/O Shuffle/O ?/O Yuk/O ,/O ikutan/O kontes/O foto/O #GayaAllEngland/O ./O Berikut/O syarat/O dan/O ketentuannya/O !/O https://t.co/SiLcYRvpbL/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O 3/O ./O Tetapi/O mengurangi/O impor/O tdk/O mudah/O ./O Dari/O situlah/O muncul/O peluang/O dan/O tantangan/O bisnis/O baru/O ./O #EconomicChallengesMetrotv/O
<43>https://t.co/T1RO5o1yQP/O Adik/O Jadi/O Atlet/O PON/ORGANIZATION 016,/O Nadia/PERSON Vega/PERSON Beri/O Dukungan/O 00/O Persen/O
@_prodem/O :/O Pemkab/O Klaten/LOCATION Dapat/O DAK/O untuk/O Perbaikan/O Saluran/O Irigasi/O https://t.co/F2tIG4UrX7/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @inung_cahyo/O :/O @infomalang/O min/O info/O dong/O tempat/O yg/O sedia/O jasa/O bikin/O mousepad/O ecer/O custom/O ukuran/O 25-30cm/O an/O panjang/O //O lebarnya/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @TheOproject/O :/O Ka/O ./O Fraksi/O @PDemokrat/O @Edhie_Baskoro/O &/O wa/O ./O ket/O DPR/ORGANIZATION Agus/PERSON Hermanto/PERSON ada/O di/O Diskusi/O Netizen/O #DemokratTolakRevisiUUKPK/O
@nifamaula/O :/O RT/O @Fitron_ihsan20/O :/O Besok/O Pagi/O (/O 2/4/O )/O Persija/ORGANIZATION Jakarta/LOCATION akan/O Uji/O coba/O melawan/O Africa/LOCATION Selection/O di/O Stadion/LOCATION Cendrawasih/LOCATION ,/O Cengkareng/LOCATION Kick/O Off/O
@AmirZulhilmi_/O :/O RT/O @himpuncrtlawak/O :/O Tidak/O mampu/O untuk/O menegur/O ./O Harap/O ini/O dapat/O membantu/O ./O Jangan/O menuntut/O di/O akhirat/O kelak/O https://t.co/ftM9lHyB4V/O
@cb_centerberita/O :/O BMKG/ORGANIZATION Aceh/LOCATION Temukan/O 3/O Titik/O Panas/O
@OctaShinta/O :/O Kodim/O Trenggalek/LOCATION Tanam/O 2000/O Pohon/O -/O Surabaya/LOCATION News/O :/O Surabaya/LOCATION News/O Kodim/O Trenggalek/LOCATION Tanam/O 2000/O https://t.co/B3zHJ6p1ee/O
<38>/O Tunjukan/O kreasi/O stickers/O asli/O hasil/O karya/O kamu/O yang/O pantas/O mejeng/O di/O BBM/ORGANIZATION Stickers!/O https://t.co/sCWbIr8O6J/O https://t.co/XF8DNy5dyp/O
<37>/O Marco/PERSON Verratti/PERSON menegaskan/O target/O utama/O Paris/ORGANIZATION Saint-Germain/ORGANIZATION (/O PSG/ORGANIZATION )/O musim/O ini/O ./O Penasaran?https://t/O .co/XbMgJnScgx/O https://t/O .co/1qvZudkn1m/O
@detikcom/O :/O Megawati/PERSON Heran/O Ahok/PERSON Hadir/O di/O Acara/O Peluncuran/O Bukunya/O https://t.co/tVpY94AyQf/O https://t.co/oq3jC7b5nq/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O oke/O mbak/O anggi/PERSON ./O nanti/O sy/O koordinasikan/O ./O https://t.co/nhwoksO2Vw/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @Rizkibgsm/O :/O Pas/O tanggal/O merah/O bengkel/O honda/ORGANIZATION (/O AHASS/O )/O di/O kota/O malang/LOCATION buka/O ga/O ya/O ?/O
@FennyTjoa/O :/O Surabaya/LOCATION ,/O Jawa/LOCATION Timur/LOCATION
@CelotehCianjur/O :/O Follow/O @LaxmiCreations/O &/O IG/O :/O LaxmiCreations/O |/O Sedia/O berbagai/O BUNGA/O RANGKAIAN/O +/O BUNGA/O PAPAN/O dll/O #FreeOngkir/O #Jakarta/O https://t.co/mnYWrIm9iL/O
@prabowo/O :/O Sejak/O awal/O berdiri/O Gerindra/ORGANIZATION kita/O sudah/O memutuskan/O berjuang/O untuk/O rakyat/O ./O Kita/O berani/O katakan/O kita/O harus/O kembali/O pada/O Pancasila/O &/O UUD/O 1945/O ./O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Total/O nasional/O DPC/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION yang/O sudah/O dilantik/O menjadi/O 2/O ./O 543/O DPC/O per/O hari/O ini/O ./O Kamis/O 25/O //O 2/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/f3dVibyI1M/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O @Pusdalops_Mlg/O @bpbdkotamalang/O https://t.co/wOmrnJU177/O
@Abu_Khalishah/O :/O Innalillah/O ./O beginilah/O susahnya/O mencari/O keadilan/O di/O negeri/O ini/O
@RSSjawatimur/O :/O Gubernur/O Jatim/LOCATION Persilakan/O Hadi/PERSON Prasetyo/PERSON Maju/O Pilkada/O
<91>/O RS/LOCATION Milik/O Rohadi/PERSON sempat/O Beroperasi/O tanpa/O Izin/O https://t/O .co/GFXK5uEpFu/O https://t/O .co/8UxO6xTGEr/O
<42>/O Taman/LOCATION Kota/LOCATION Turunkan/O Tingkat/O Stres/O Warga/O Surabaya/LOCATION ./O https://t/O .co/KYKiahoOzA/O
@radityadika/O :/O Latihan/O membaca/O skenario/O film/O Koala/O Kumal/O dgn/O Acha/PERSON Septriasa/PERSON ./O Di/O filmnya/O dia/O jadi/O ,/O ehm/O ,/O pacar/O gue/O ./O https://t.co/B90lsmOIJi/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Hai/O @StandUpBJM/O ,/O jangan/O lupa/O datang/O ke/O Jagonya/O Comic/O The/O Battle/O yg/O dipersembahkan/O @KFCINDONESIA/O #Ad/O https://t.co/EYmt31Xyyh/O
@BKNSquare/O :/O PT./ORGANIZATION IRAWAN/ORGANIZATION DJAJA/ORGANIZATION AGUNG/ORGANIZATION
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Jangan/O bekerja/O untuk/O orang/O yang/O tidak/O menghormati/O waktu/O Anda/O untuk/O keluarga/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O datang/O ke/O Puskesmas/LOCATION Kuok/LOCATION memastikan/O korban/O bencana/O asap/O mendapatkan/O pelayanan/O kesehatan/O dengan/O baik/O -/O Jkw/PERSON http://t.co/AMg1XhXj3l/O
@Syamewl_19/O :/O @HamkaKey/O @dalilikhnpiah_/O siapa/O sekolah/O mana/O ?/O
<31>/O @jokowi/O terima/O kasih/O Pak/O ,/O siap/O wujudkan./O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O Taman/LOCATION Bugar//LOCATION Merjosari/LOCATION CSR/O PT/ORGANIZATION NikkoSteel/ORGANIZATION diresmikan/O Walikota/O Mlg/LOCATION ./O Polisi/O Taman/O dr/O DKP/ORGANIZATION siap/O amankan/O taman2/O di/O Kota/O Mlg/LOCATION https://t.co/HLAKqppFyW/O
@Dalila__Omar/O :/O RT/O @Tizznasuha/O :/O Aku/O masa/O 3/O bulan/O
@SBYess/O :/O RT/O @MasSoftwareId/O :/O SEMINAR/O SOFTWARE/O AKUNTANSI/O !/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @Pusdalops_Mlg/O :/O @pemkotmalang/O https://t.co/3TLPCS8r4I/O
@JKT48FC/O :/O Bukan/O hanya/O itu/O ,/O @Nadilavatic_ID/O pun/O juga/O memberi/O subsidi/O tiket/O di/O event/O hs/O Surabaya/LOCATION ./O Tapi/O hanya/O hs/O dengan/O Nadila/PERSON sebesar/O 15rb/tiket/O ./O
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O kagum/O dg/O kegigihan/O Bu/O Purwati/PERSON ,/O pembuat/O abon/O ikan/O mata/O goyang/O ./O Ada/O yg/O pernah/O lihat/O ikan/O itu/O ?/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/JXSrjNrKKh/O
@Idol2014Ubay/O :/O Tak/O terbukti/O bersalah/O ,/O Seorang/O siswa/O tidak/O mau/O "/O MENUNTUT/O "/O Ilmu/O
@radityadika/O :/O Ngeliatin/O kebo/O kumpul/O siang2/O ./O ./O https://t.co/5S189VGuWU/O
@aidil_gassing/O :/O PADANG/LOCATION -/O Kabupaten/O Solok/LOCATION ,/O Sumatera/LOCATION Barat/LOCATION ,/O diterjang/O banjir/O dan/O longsor/O di/O Jorong/LOCATION Kasiak/LOCATION https://t.co/dYk7akpXQW/O
@aagym/O :/O Ikhlas/O itu/O sebuah/O perjalanan/O perjuangan/O ,/O Alloh/O menghargai/O setiap/O upaya/O kita/O berusaha/O untuk/O ikhlas/O https://t.co/FQtLIPSPOi/O
@radityadika/O :/O Selamat/O siang/O ./O ./O https://t.co/kFB4OXsb3l/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Selanjutnya/O soal/O pembangunan/O infrastruktur/O pendukung/O ekonomi/O ,/O negara/O kita/O negara/O kepulauan/O maka/O harus/O diperbanyak/O lanud/O &/O pelabuhan/O ./O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Sebelum/O Tewas/O ,/O Syahrul/PERSON Gunawan/PERSON Sempat/O Minta/O Uang/O https://t.co/LgrhqbVspz/O
<8>/O Gol/O "Injury/O Time"/O Menangkan/O Arsenal/ORGANIZATION ./O https://t/O .co/baxQvx6ggg/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Dlm/O rangka/O transparansi/O pengelolaan/O dana/O CSR/Hibah/O utk/O pembangunan/O kota/O Bdg/LOCATION silakan/O kunjungi/O https://t.co/tglVbdDga5/O https://t.co/awUsioU0pu/O
@radityadika/O :/O Betul/O ./O https://t.co/M1hqdV1YWY/O
@inmalangraya/O :/O Kocak/O !/O Jelang/O Final/O Piala/O Bhayangkara/O 2016/O ,/O Wali/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION dan/O Bandung/LOCATION Sepakat/O Taruhan/O https://t.co/5n2eiR8rn2/O
@farizarias/O :/O @JNECare/O mau/O nanya/O ,/O sy/O ngirim/O paketan/O ke/O kantor/O jne/ORGANIZATION surabaya/LOCATION jl/LOCATION ./O Karimun/LOCATION jawa/LOCATION no/O 25-27/O surabaya/LOCATION ./O Nah/O tapi/O saya/O nggak/O tau/O kalo/O [/O 1/2/O ]/O
@daniaaal/O :/O @kimnaise/O @hzwnsryn/O jangan/O putus/O ASA/O ya/O kawan-kawan/O ./O Marilah/O kita/O berDAMAI/O supaya/O semangat/O gotong-royong/O itu/O ada/O sesama/O kita/O
@detikcom/O :/O Elite/O PDIP/ORGANIZATION Minta/O Menhub/O Jonan/PERSON Mundur/O https://t.co/L2bz1hy5gj/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAlife_/O :/O Tips/O Pakai/O Choker/O Ala/O Supermodel/O https://t.co/tnlH26K42T/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Benar/O ./O Sejak/O awal/O sudah/O kami/O @FPD_DPR/O minta/O &/O himbau/O utk/O menyerahkan/O LHKPN/O ke/O @KPK_RI/O sesuai/O batas/O waktu/O ./O ./O https://t.co/6mYsPFoRgD/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @Dinsos_Malang/O :/O @retria/O @pemkotmalang/O baik/O sdh/O kami/O tindak/O lanjuti/O ./O saat/O ini/O dalam/O proses/O ./O anak/O tsbt/O dlm/O pantauan/O dan/O tlh/O dilakukan/O
@aagym/O :/O Jangan/O suka/O mempersulit/O diri/O ,/O semua/O ujian/O sudah/O diukur/O oleh/O Alloh/O ,/O Alloh/O mustahil/O berbuat/O zolim/O kepada/O siapapun/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVA_log/O :/O Nasi/O Liwet/O dan/O Sate/O Maranggi/O Enak/O di/O Lembang/LOCATION https://t.co/lD1R9V6ZSl/O
@detikcom/O :/O Nikmati/O Soto/O Betawi/O yang/O Gurih/O Hangat/O di/O 5/O Tempat/O Ini/O https://t.co/cv5JJRtXQp/O via/O @detikfood/O https://t.co/ajejNLajFf/O
@radityadika/O :/O Muncul/O lagi/O dia/O ./O ./O https://t.co/7O3aqybmic/O
@detikcom/O :/O Menggemaskan/O Sih/O ,/O Tapi/O Anak/O Gemuk/O Lebih/O Berisiko/O Terkena/O Penyakit/O https://t.co/t4PdUtsqdF/O via/O @detikHealth/O https://t.co/B35rG5GY31/O
@reusdianto/O :/O @se_bdg/O @JakartaItuBiru/O @BIG_AH/O @BobotohID/O 2/O ada/O ?/O Posisi/O tapi/O di/O jakarta/LOCATION waa/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Alutsista/O Indonesia/LOCATION termasuk/O yang/O paling/O terbelakang/O bahkan/O di/O antara/O beberapa/O tetangga/O negara/O ASEAN/ORGANIZATION ./O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O Hadapi/O Inggris/LOCATION ,/O Jerman/LOCATION Tanpa/O 3/O Pilar/O ?/O https://t.co/7ngU4xTBFm/O
@jokowi/O :/O Saya/O bertemu/O dengan/O warga/O Indonesia/LOCATION di/O Amerika/LOCATION Serikat/LOCATION ./O Hangat/O dan/O terasa/O semangat/O ke-Indonesiaan-nya/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/uSEonbHDOL/O
@kalimsafitri/O :/O RT/O @TMG_NET/O :/O Nah/O sekarang/O giliran/O ke/O rumah/LOCATION bastian/PERSON deh/O pak/O RT/O sama/O ucup/PERSON ngabarin/O kalo/O ada/O latihan/O simulasi/O gempa/O https://t.co/CFS6RjbgoA/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Wanita/O yang/O menunjukkan/O tanda-tanda/O akan/O memaafkan/O jika/O diselingkuhi/O ,/O akan/O diselingkuhi/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Mengunjungi/O nelayan/O Partai/O Perindo/ORGANIZATION di/O Pantai/LOCATION Purus/LOCATION ./O Padang/LOCATION ,/O Rabu/O ,/O 9/O Maret/O 2016/O https://t.co/F8ZKZQ7nCG/O
@radityadika/O :/O Sampai/O di/O Lombok/LOCATION ,/O langsung/O rebahan/O di/O hotelnya/O ./O ./O https://t.co/Uw6T1mAM35/O
@Metro_TV/O :/O Ahok/PERSON Tuding/O Taksi/O Daring/O &/O Taksi/O Konvesional/O Langgar/O Aturan/O https://t.co/xgT8gundqO/O https://t.co/dou9hhiwCH/O
@KompasTV/O :/O Ini/O Pesan/O Kapolri/O untuk/O Kapolda/O dan/O Perwira/O Polri/ORGANIZATION https://t.co/Cqxri2nJGw/O
@detikcom/O :/O Polisi/ORGANIZATION akan/O Telusuri/O Dugaan/O Pelanggaran/O Hukum/O Hotel/LOCATION Club/LOCATION Bali/LOCATION yang/O Longsor/O https://t.co/axowWtBHGQ/O
@togepict/O :/O Avail/O Booking/O @amel_jogja/O Area/O :/O JOGJAKARTA/LOCATION Hub/O :/O Mention/DM/O Expo/O :/O -/O https://t.co/PyK3E3ZGfK/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Menerima/O cenderamata/O dari/O Datuk/PERSON Seri/PERSON Ahmad/PERSON Zahid/PERSON Bin/PERSON Hamidi/PERSON ,/O Wakil/O Presiden/O UMNO/ORGANIZATION ./O Kinabalu/LOCATION ,/O Malaysia/LOCATION ,/O Sabtu/O 5/O //O 3/O //O 2016/O https://t.co/6avaUgLHRf/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Turut/O berduka/O cita/O atas/O berpulangnya/O tokoh/O kreatif/O Indonesia/LOCATION dan/O sahabat/O membangun/O BDG/LOCATION ,/O kang/O Tegep/PERSON Oktaviansyah/PERSON ./O https://t.co/I9wvBO2Xdw/O
@syazrienax/O :/O Menuntut/O ke/O ?/O hahahahahah/O
@devillixous/O :/O Yakali/O kelas/O 12/O UN/O gua/O disuruh/O masuk/O sekolah/O ./O Pak/O beri/O kami/O libur/O pak/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @Adis_Prayoga/O :/O mau/O tanya/O ,/O tempat/O service/O jam/O automatic/O di/O malang/LOCATION dimana/O ?/O @infomalang/O
@infodishub/O :/O SERTIJAB/PERSON ,/O MANGINDAAN/PERSON dan/O JONAN/PERSON SEPAKAT/O SOAL/O KEUTAMAAN/O MULTIMODA/O http://t.co/VdssE8SZqG/O #BeritaPusat/O
@aagym/O :/O Setiap/O malam/O Jumat/O Aa/O ada/O kajian/O Tauhid/O di/O daaruttauhiid/LOCATION
@infomalang/O :/O @Vegaramadhan/O coba/O laporkan/O keluhan/O dan/O nomor/O pelanggannya/O ke/O @pdammalangkota/O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O Mari/O kita/O mulai/O debat/O bernegara/O konvensi/O calon/O presiden/O @PDemokrat/O ,/O mohon/O doa/O dan/O dukungannya/O ,/O Salam/O 55/O !/O
@_Broken_Home_/O :/O RT/O @SalsabillaAzhie/O :/O @Tha5SOSFamily/O AYO/O KELUARGA/O !/O
@Metro_TV/O :/O Alasan/O Peserta/O Cairkan/O Dana/O JHT/O Makin/O Beragam/O https://t.co/1251PTHYyK/O https://t.co/hWevrp5i3u/O
<56>/O #Lifestyle/O #Kemenpar/O Genjot/O Wisata/O ,/O Lampung/LOCATION Gelar/O Festival/O Taman/O Hutan/O Raya/O https://t.co/1QzYHi1tor/O https://t.co/mjK8VXJtyy/O
@MRDSuryadi98/O :/O RT/O @dwiii_pangestu/O :/O Senyum/O itu/O ibadah/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Adik-adik/O yang/O saya/O sayangi/O ,/O pagi-pagi/O gini/O enaknya/O kita/O cool/O tweet/O tentang/O apa/O ya/O ?/O
@zuhayraaaa/O :/O tak/O guna/O dpt/O tapi/O
@prabowo/O :/O Selamat/O bertugas/O kepada/O Danjen/O Kopassus/ORGANIZATION yang/O baru/O ,/O saudara/O Mayjen/O TNI/ORGANIZATION Doni/PERSON Monardo/PERSON ./O Berani/O ,/O benar/O ,/O berhasil/O !/O http://t.co/VZpsmX119P/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O Usai/O Sholat/O Istisqa/O di/O Masjid/LOCATION Istiqlal/LOCATION Jakarta/LOCATION ,/O Ahad/O (/O 1/O //O 11/O )/O ,/O semoga/O hujan/O yg/O membawa/O berkah/O segera/O turun/O ,/O Aamiin/O https://t.co/9taxLTs8ra/O
@rommelsilitonga/O :/O Raffi/PERSON -/O Nagita/PERSON Bangga/O Brand/O Wonderful/O Indonesia/LOCATION :/O JAKARTA/LOCATION (/O Pos/O Kota/O )/O Satu/O demi/O satu/O ,/O artis-artis/O muda/O Indonesia/LOCATION https://t.co/SmP3WquIBL/O
@infomalang/O :/O RT/O @Haemorrhage22/O :/O Permisi/O min/O ,/O mau/O tanya/O tempat/O penyewaan/O ps3/O dmna/O ya/O ?/O Sekalian/O cp/O nya/O
@CelotehDEPOK/O :/O Follow/O @LaxmiCreations/O &/O IG/O :/O LaxmiCreations/O |/O Sedia/O berbagai/O BUNGA/O RANGKAIAN/O +/O BUNGA/O PAPAN/O dll/O #FreeOngkir/O #Jakarta/O https://t.co/fXqiWwSpdd/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O RT/O @FPD_DPR/O :/O di/O Pabrik/ORGANIZATION Garmen/ORGANIZATION Tasikmalaya/LOCATION ,/O SBY/PERSON dan/O Ibas/PERSON Serap/O Aspirasi/O ,/O https://t.co/vZCJhbcbG5/O @SBYudhoyono/O @Edhie_Baskoro/O
@rn_ah2/O :/O RT/O @melly_goeslaw/O :/O Tadi/O malam/O Baju/O putih/O cantik/O ini/O dari/O @isis_jakarta/O Photo/O by/O @putradjohan/O Make/O up/O dhirmanputra/O https://t.co/RrmYdQzD42/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Politikus/O Senior/O Golkar/ORGANIZATION :/O ARB/PERSON -/O Agung/PERSON Kayak/O Amplop/O dan/O Prangko/O https://t.co/sUnDMWURi1/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Lalu/O ada/O keluarga/O yang/O merasa/O lebih/O ningrat/O daripada/O tetangganya/O ,/O karena/O ada/O anaknya/O yang/O sarjana/O ,/O walau/O pun/O masih/O menganggur/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
<70>/O Tangkap/O Pemimpin/O Unjuk/O Rasa/O ,/O Polisi/O Serbu/O Desa/LOCATION Wukan/O https://t/O .co/0JVM5J0tpv/O https://t/O .co/grLbTW9Hxg/O
@radityadika/O :/O Meeting/O produksi/O film/O Koala/O Kumal/O ./O ./O https://t.co/hx2YUQl6jn/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Fraksi/O PDIP/ORGANIZATION Sudah/O Inginkan/O Pembangunan/O Masela/O di/O Darat/O https://t.co/BFVc3XIyiw/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O 1/O ./O Pemerintah/O tetap/O berkomitmen/O menurunkan/O suku/O bungan/O KUR/O dari/O 22/O %/O menjadi/O 12/O %/O thn/O ini/O #munaskadin/O
@infoBMKG/O :/O Hal/O ini/O karena/O waktu/O selesainya/O #GMT9Mar16/O di/O Jayapura/LOCATION adalah/O yang/O paling/O akhir/O di/O Indonesia/LOCATION
<24>/O Kala/O Pogba/PERSON Dibanjiri/O SMS/O dan/O Telepon/O dari/O Mourinho/PERSON ./O https://t/O .co/nyiWaLMknd/O
@prabowo/O :/O Ketenangan/O politik/O akan/O terwujud/O kalau/O demokrasi/O dihormati/O dan/O dijalankan/O ./O Tak/O boleh/O ada/O akal-akalan/O terhadap/O hukum/O &/O demokrasi/O ./O #1TahunKMP/O
@e10febi/O :/O Kumpulan/O Foto/O Terbaru/O Artis/O Cantik/O Yuki/PERSON Kato/PERSON :/O https://t.co/4tS8maRS7f/O
@husniafwina/O :/O Komersialisasi/O Pendidikan/O Tinggi/O ./O
@edhiewibowo_55/O :/O @faisalyusra/O alhamdulillah/O semua/O baik/O saja/O ./O
<19>https://t.co/eVN4VCfqHP/O Dibuat/O Ulang,/O Serial/O MacGyver/O Bakal/O Obati/O Kangen/O Generasi/O 90-an/O
@Metro_TV/O :/O BPJS/ORGANIZATION Ketenagakerjaan/ORGANIZATION Resmi/O Buka/O Layanan/O 7/O Hari/O Kerja/O https://t.co/YhMtQUAUGg/O https://t.co/r8HNH8cvZ0/O
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Tegaslah/O dalam/O keputusanmu/O ./O yang/O kau/O lakukan/O lebih/O penting/O daripada/O semua/O keraguan/O dan/O rasa/O takutmu/O ./O Mario/PERSON Teguh/PERSON
@MTLovenHoney/O :/O Katakanlah/O Aamiin/O atau/O Retweet/O ,/O jika/O doa/O senja/O ini/O adalah/O doa/O Anda/O juga/O ./O https://t.co/v2MgTnocFR/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O Advokat/O Cemaskan/O Tren/O Kriminalisasi/O Calon/O Kepala/O Daerah/O https://t.co/ncSOdzbqkq/O
<26>/O Chelsea/ORGANIZATION kemungkinan/O besar/O tanpa/O John/PERSON Terry/PERSON saat/O menjamu/O Liverpool/ORGANIZATION ./O Ada/O apa/O dgn/O John/PERSON Tery/PERSON ?https://t/O .co/SM9H0tKzWF/O https://t/O .co/yBNotjVvxn/O
@IssacNade/O :/O Dirgahayu/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION tercinta/O ./O kota/O dingin/O yang/O selalu/O ku/O rindukan/O ./O #102NuhatKotaMalang/O https://t.co/l82D0Hgi9s/O
@detiksport/O :/O Dua/O Laga/O Awal/O Benitez/PERSON di/O Newcastle/ORGANIZATION :/O Kalah/O 0-1/O ,/O lalu/O Seri/O 1-1/O https://t.co/1abpekGsxZ/O
@pemkotmalang/O :/O RT/O @FaruQ_IkkYuUDha/O :/O hujan2/O walikota/O malang/LOCATION menyambut/O para/O tukang/O becak/O untuk/O memberikan/O sembako/O kepada/O mereka/O @pemkotmalang/O
@prabowo/O :/O Sahabat/O ,/O marilah/O kita/O sama-sama/O berdoa/O agar/O semua/O amal/O ibadah/O beliau/O selama/O ini/O diterima/O dan/O keluarga/O yang/O ditinggalkan/O diberikan/O kekuatan/O ./O
@KicauPulitik/O :/O Malang/LOCATION Resmi/O Gelar/O Pameran/O Kota/O Kreatif/O https://t.co/ZOXJziS45q/O #KicauPulitik/O
@VIVAcoid/O :/O RT/O @VIVAbola/O :/O '/O Ibrahimovic/PERSON Akhiri/O Karier/O Saya/O di/O Timnas/O Inggris/LOCATION '/O https://t.co/zFSkoNWwFH/O
@ridwankamil/O :/O Warga/O Bdg/LOCATION ,/O besok/O semua/O PKL/O di/O jl/LOCATION Purnawarman/LOCATION akan/O ditata/O dan/O dipindahkan/O ke/O lokasi/O baru/O ./O Pejalankaki/O akan/O nyaman/O lg/O ./O https://t.co/e4uBmOFwRQ/O
@Edhie_Baskoro/O :/O Selamat/O #HariIbu/O ./O Terimakasih/O utk/O para/O ibu/O yg/O selalu/O membimbing/O keluarga/O dgn/O cinta/O &/O kasih/O sayang/O #YoureTheBest/O #Mom/O https://t.co/BXYhChtH7X/O
@Pak_JK/O :/O 1/O ./O Kami/O sepakat/O dengan/O Presiden/O untuk/O menuntaskan/O kasus/O pencatutan/O nama/O Presiden/O dan/O Wapres/O ./O
@luqmannaim09/O :/O RT/O @______aisya/O :/O "/O Akak/O kenapa/O sekolah/O menengah/O wajib/O buat/O ketupat/O ?/O Dia/O lukis/O ketupat/O wehhhhhh/O ketupat/O https://t.co/kEdUbi2CRn/O
@key_think/O :/O wong/O indonesia/LOCATION apal/O lagu/O indonesia/LOCATION raya/O ki/O wes/O biasa/O kang/O ./O seng/O luar/O biasa/O nek/O ra/O apal/O kui/O ./O wkkkkk/O https://t.co/WM0Fm3gdDR/O
@Hary_Tanoe/O :/O Bright/O Awards/O memberikan/O apresiasi/O bagi/O dunia/O periklanan/O yang/O merupakan/O industri/O kreatif/O ,/O agar/O mereka/O terus/O bertumbuh/O https://t.co/fOb1SQGUAF/O
@jokowi/O :/O Menyapa/O dan/O mendengar/O aspirasi/O petani/O di/O Desa/LOCATION Tomo/LOCATION ,/O Sumedang/LOCATION ./O Semoga/O panen/O kali/O ini/O bawa/O keuntungan/O bagi/O petani/O -/O Jkw/PERSON https://t.co/Igt9WfeFx3/O
@KarebaPinrang/O :/O Menuju/O desa/O yg/O berbudaya/O bersih/O ,/O wrga/O Desa/O Patobong/LOCATION adkan/O gotong/O royong/O ,/O info/O kami/O kutip/O dri/O https://t.co/VcwUqPSnnk/O https://t.co/RkQIhpiaLJ/O
@hariankompas/O :/O Pusat/O Ekonomi/O Baru/O Didorong/O "/O Konferensi/O Kota-kota/O Kreatif/O 2016/O Digelar/O di/O Kota/O Malang/LOCATION https://t.co/RSDlkWlvBv/O https://t.co/dpjoIFM2ys/O
